the tongue only describes a little pain,
but deep pains are speechless
I'm also speechless since left me to go to my mom's last place,dad
you wanted so..
I'm leaving for you guys to be in peaceful in heaven
I packed  up everything I have,to go Istanbul...to be quiet
Aunt?
I have arrived..
whoa!
ah! husband Tayyar,didn't you go to the terminal.how is she gonna find our home all the way from Harem
we have left her alone in terminal
we already opened our home doors for her to stay with us
I'm not gonna welcome someone that I don't want to stay in my home
she should have come with us long time ago
Tayyar!her father was sick she cant leave her father alone..what can she do
Listen,all she has now is us.being unwilling is not nice
look at me! I don't want you to give her indulgence
you don't want her to be spoil in the first day of her over here,okay
say repentance Tayyar why are you saying like she is just a people
she is my nephew
don't even start saying that she is your nephew crap
shame on you...
are you giving me answer?!
I wanna beat you up!
Tayyar..
I accidently hit the bowl with my hand Ms Aytul..
cleaning up right away
make Mr. Yigit's car ready Tayyar
will do it now! Ms. Aytul
look at me now! I'm already doing favor that chick by letting her stay here.she will be thankful and quiet,get it?
Kozan,Kozan farm is still ahead?
we passed like 2 km miss
I told you to let me know why didn't you?stop let me out then
her father passed away why he keep hating on him I don't understand
he calls her people like she is someone else
she is a trust from my older brother after he passed away
of course I want her to be near me
oh! my dear I'm cleaning up the table,you ate already right?
I did I did
Elmas..you don't be like your dad on her okay? please don't let her feel alone her okay?she is your uncle's daughter
mom please don't start in the morning
also I have very important meeting with my boss Yigit don't keep me busy
I still have to organize files
I'm worried Mr. Yigit drives car too fast
that's his hobby...
look!
bro are we dreaming?
an angel without wings in the middle of the forest!
did you get lost?
did you swallow your tongue?
let me give you a ride
or you didn't like us?
get lost!
bro she is aggressive
i told you guys go away
what if we not leave?
keep driving
come here don't be scared
where are you going to?
help!!!
please help!!
don't get close!
oh we scared a lot now
come on stop doing affecttation
whats going on here?
its not your business
abi thats Mr yigit
they are running away do something about it
call police please
i will press charge them
oh so you hero game is till here huh?
you let them run away
what kind of place i came to?what kind of sick people are you guys
is this how you say thank you?
you want me to thank you for the game you played with your friend?
my friends??
are you paranoiac ?
really?
2 minutes ago i was attacked by those bandits
now the leader of the group let them run away
but after all I'm still paranoiac right?
the leader of bandits?
these bandits are my friends?
i thought i helped you out
yeah right you Istanbul people are so helpful anyway
wherever you are from.you are so sweet talker...you okay?
don't approach
do whatever you want then
you look like lost,where are you trying to go?
not your business
I'm trying to help you out
i don't want you help
stop dragging this
this is forest
don't approach
look! there is no car,taxi or bus passing by on this road
you cant find anything over here
few km ahead starts picnic area
if you are lucky you can probably find drunk people partying
cant you ever stop?
cant you ever listen?
look
last call
where are you going?
im going to God damn Kozan's farm,okay!
you are going to wrong way,wrong
did i ask you to navigate me?
please stop arguing
i will take you there
what is you problem?
what do you want from me?? i don't need any help
you cant find the farm like this,hop in
are you maniac?
crazy?
no need help!
what are you doing you crazy maniac
help!
stop the car!
now what? we are going to God damn Kozan's farm
you psychopath
i wan to get out let me out
are you sick?why don't you let me go?
enjoy the meal.
anything else Ms Aytul?
no thanks
I already prepared the ground beef for the little man,should i cook pasty or meatballs?
he keep saying beatballs since in the morning,you make her meatballs
he can eat pastry with us in the dinner with us
okay.
where did we come to?
whats going on Hafize?
its Mr yigit's car
he has someone next to him but..
oh my god Nur!
Hafize whats the hell is going on?
slow down! you crazy!
whoa!
i will sue you!!
you kidnapped me!
aunt!?
Elmas?!
welcome to god damn Kozan's farm..
how did you get here?
welcome..
Yigit what's going on?
ha Elmas...
your cousin has arrived
you are off today
but there was a meeting, i can see her in the evening
Nur?
alright
you are off.
oh...
Tayyar
her luggage in on the side of the our road
could you let someone get it?
sure! right now!
i kept being in panic how she will get here.i mean,i i was figuring out how she would get here for 40 years i would never knew you would get here with Mr yigit car.
aunt?
the person you were always telling me about that guy name Yigit Kozan was this guy?he is like bandit!
ssshh keep silent girl
how can you call him bandit?
we make money for living from him
hmmm.you said everything bad stuff to him
i should have done more!
how are we gonna look Ms Aytul's face?
anyways get ready and lets go to thank them for letting you to stay here
i didn't even get a chance to hug you
did my brother said god damn kozan's farm?
she got a big mouth
but she is beautiful
you are letting her stay in out home but...
hopefully she wont make is regret Ms aytul
this is Kozan's farm
everyone should know their level
if not they will learn to know that
be good my girl okay?
be very nice and polite to her she is the boss of the house
she is also Yigit's half mom,also his aunt,also...
also?
that's all you just be nice to her
Ms aytul my nephew Nur
we so regretful that she has arrived here with a big noise but
she would like to kiss your hand if you would let her
go ahead my girl
that's fine
welcome
thank you
Hafize
giver her some clothes so she doesn't walk around with her chest open
i apologize
my bottons was broken when i was trying to escape from your nephew
why are you giving her answer
are you gonna get me in trouble?
lets go to the kitchen
you happy
i am
but I'm late gotta go now
looks like you will be busy
should we wait you for a dinner?
no don't wait for me i will come late
all day you gonna be at the office?
yes
i was thinking maybe if you get a chance we can go to visit but...
where is Mert?
in his room
he is punished
he should already be a good kid since he is in the first grade of school
he had a report for half semester
he didn't go to school since that
he became more perky,everyday different problems he makes
don't indulgence on him
once you do,he get more agressive
okay
i will talk to him
grandma i have a surprise can you come to my room please?
mert?
look at him
what was that noise?
dad were you here?
yeah iam
what happened?
out little Mr is set a trap for us
obviously
son.didn't you get over your grandma's punishments?
even i did but you haven't
i did but..
but what?
you did but you are keep doing it
come here
look my boy.be good okay?
I'm getting mad
im not doing these stuff to make you guys mad,im doing it to make my mom mad at me
if she sees that i'm being bad boy so she can see it to come get mad at me
why do you say like this
look
look at me
no pranking in house okay?
be a grown man
and next time don't say stuff like this about your mom
give me a man word?
man word
stop! you didn't take my drawing today
this big guy is you in here
the one is an angel is mom
her wings are so big
she clapped her wings and came to see us
you gave me a man word
don't forget
there is a pond you see it?
and then...
behind there is ranch
we have everything here including cows and sheep as you understand
very nice
just like our village
my dad would have been happy to see it
yeah..
just like our place
in Istanbul but away from the town
anyways,once weekend arrive we can take you to real istanbul
if you ever get stuck in this farm like my mom,you cant say that you live in stanbul
you look like bored of being here
to be honest if Mr yigit wasn't existing if would probably blasted in here
i work with him as you know
at Kozan's
in a huge plaza
in the middle of town called Levent
in the belly of civilization as you understand
i will drive
what an aggressive man
he looks like he is upset of something
i feel bad for you.it must be tough for you to work with this guy
i cant really say that Mr Yigit is the easiest person in the world
but he is the biggest chance in my live
the only chance to work with him
he is very nice guy
he looks like he think himself only with his money
you shouldn't think that he was born with the money
he was created his own luck
ripped off his luck by himself
step by step he went to target by himself
he was never surrender to anyone
he was grown without mother and father in huge Istanbul
who knows...
the money he has probably nothing comparing the sweat back then
he is big man, very big...obviously if a person get big as him gets tough as well of course.
but his inside is different
macho tough and as like you said sometimes he is unpolite
but his inside is very different
with his son he is completely different person
he has son?
i wish his wife patience then
his wife was the one in curly hair??
no way!
that witch is a wife of his brother Cahit
stop gossiping girl
Nur my dear
you are tired after long way,take a bath and rest
and since you are off change your clothes and help me out
auntie i can help you out
no my dear you are tired you go ahead
alright
look at me what were you guys talking about?
Mr yigit up and down huh?
i hope you didn't tell her about that
mom.for the love of the god take a breath
of course i didn't
please my daughter don't get us in a trouble, if Mr yigit finds out will find ourself at the outdoor
really?
because i never learned what to say and what not to say
also i know more what Mr. Yigit is sensitive about from any of your guys
unbelievable
ah my dear you are tired.you should have Elmas serve for us
you think she will be tired from morning till evening Hafize?
of course she will do it.she wont just sleep in this house
also let her help you in the kitchen tomorrow
and talk to Ms Aytul
let put her as stooge
i can always hep my aunt
and you don't need to ask anyone to help me find a job
i will search for a job tomorrow
hmm,hehehe
you will search for a job?
girl!
this is Istanbul not Adana
over here,the bread is in the lion's stomach not in the mouth
especially person like you never seen university
oh
if you think to make money in a different way,then i don't know..
incase if you didn't come to earn your money with the right way
incase if you think you will make money with your young and beauty,that i don't know
forgive the god,what kind of conversation are you talking about Mr Tayyar
i just wanted to warn her in the beginning so i don't get in trouble...look me me girl.
if you came here to make money with your beauty then i will have serious business,just to let you know
i didn't come here to believe my beauty,came here to believe my knowledgement
you don't worry
speaking of that Nur,what happened your school?
first i will find a job to make enough money for myself
and then i will continue my university hopefully
hopefully
you would probably want to move out your own place in the future too
right?
hopefully that will happen too
i don't want to be a weight for you guys
you see what happened your officer income father?
he became a dirt
his daughter became a shelter of Tayyar's home that never liked me
enjoy the meal guys
i will get some fresh air
please don't play with your food,come on finish your plate
i don't want to eat
my dad still haven't arrived home
he left himself hungry  tonight too
of course he ate,he probably eating outside
your dad is works for you too
i have everything why he still working?
what do you have a lion of his uncle? huh? because your dad works right?
can my dad get anything by working?
of course he can
if he can get anything,why doesn't he get back here my mom from the heaven?
lets go little boy
since you don't eat lets go brush teeth and go to the bed
looks like we wont be able to send this kid to school for this semester too
yigit will need to get another report
what are you talking you Nazan?
you probably didn't realized Ms aytul but your grandson is still expecting his mother from heaven
you thing that yigit wont be worried if he still talks weird stuff like this?
if he gets someone's attention,or i don't know
what if someone tells him the truth
Nazan you mind you own business
i hope yigit wont come home in the morning
did you talk to him after you left the office Cahit?
i knocked his door but he didn't respond
you didn't get respond but you didn't think to open his door right Cahit?
you little brother didn't let you in?
i didn't want to disturb him Nazan
it get cold overe here at night
you can catch the cold
by the way my name is Yigit
i know your name
we are talking polite after calling me names
i know your name too but we haven't met yet right?
i thought i met you in the car
im Nur
get inside if you like
its cold
don't catch cold
have a good night
and the you will be brother,without getting permission to enter into you own brother's room
you can only knock to door to your own brothers door
you are the older one Cahit
where is Mert? here?
i just put him in the bed brother
aunt,is Mert with you in downstairs?
girl,you saying you out him in to bed,where is this kid?
what happened Yigit?
Mert isn't in his room,have you seen ?
what happened?
or he...
run run
mom?
im here mommy
mommy im here
come to me
come on
im here
Mert!!
where are you at?
be calm Yigit
calm for what?
all of you guys adult cant even watch for a little kid
i told you to lock him in his room but you never listen
mert
mert?
how did you get up there?
don't be scared okay im coming up there
dont even move
i want my mom
come to me
brother he is here
where
Mert ehat are you doin up there?
dont let my dad come here he will bring me down
stop stop his dad
we will go down now
dont even move im coming
im not scared my mom will come now
im not scared
dont even move there
come on Mert bring me your hand
no i want to hold my mom's hand
come on
okay
come to me
hug me tight now
hold on daddy we coming down
okay pass him to me
come here
what do you think you are doing? ha!
what do you think you are doing?
you wont do this again,understand me?
you wont
i will,untill my mom comes here
you mom wont come
understand you mom aint come back
you are liar,my mom will come back
you told me that she will come back from the clouds,stars,and heaven
no she wont!
stop it!
stop yelling at him
give me my grandson
come here my boy
he will not get out of his room
heard me all?
Yigit please calm down
brother you stop please
what is this doing in here?who put this up here
i was gonna trim the tree but we forgot it here
dont event start and bring me to saw,now!
ok
Nur?
im coming aunt let me take some fresh air first
seems like he is missing his mom so much,why you are not being understanding?
Tayyar
where is the saw
coming sir
here you go
what are you doing you are crazy or what?
move on
you punished you son already,now you wanna punish the tree?
told you to move dont get in
if you think you fear will go away like this?
you locked him to his room,now your fear is gone?
you are afraid
instead of understanding you son you are punishing him you will still be scared
i hate my dad
why does he says that my mom wont come back?
why heaven isn't giving us back to my mom?why??
its like the kid will be in my dream tonight saying mom mom while reaching out the tree
it doesn't go away front of my eyes
what happened to his mom?
traffic accident
3 years ago
he misses his mom a lot
he doesn't accept that his mom is dead
he this she will be back
feel bad about him
why you dont want to understand Iclal,why?
it doesn't work out and it wont work out
you know that we started with a mistake
everything was set by my aunt
i love you Yigit
iclal,you love me.then why our life is a hell for us,why?
why are we waking up every morning with a fight?
look Iclal,i wan to divorce from you
understand?
you want to divorce me right?
yes
you want to life the life without me right?
but for me there is no life without you Yigit.if you are not the one for me then no life for me
what are you doing Iclal.let it go
Iclal can open her eyes anytime,she can open her eyes now or after years..
or she will never wake up
3 years.3years the only thing you guys make me memorized is when a mother of my son will wake up
when?
time is ticking
your wife would be always sleeping too
we all get wound while living...big, small, deep
we all have many wounds in our life..
time makes some of the wound become shell
some of them hard to see,or cant feel it
but some of them even though only scar left,it still can be bleeding...
time cant be a medicine on some of the wounds...
it hides from the eyes but not from the heart
Yigit Kozan...
arrogant,
rough,
brutal man
you have a big wound too
like me..
dad!dad!
balloon tree
for you,son!
Mert your feet are naked!
dad?
son you feet naked you will catch cold
be carefull dont catch anything sharp under your feet
good boy
dad did you do this for me?
yea of course for you
aren't you gonna get mad at me if i come up there?
why would i son? come up here
but you got mad at me last night?
but now im here
peace?
peace.
listen me now,from now wherever you go,
to the trees,to the clouds,to the sun
where ever you go dont leave your dad's hand,deal?
deal
good boy
lets wave at my mom now
daddy can we can a balloon to my mom?
lets do it
here
wait
lets do it together when i say 3 okay
one two three
say hi to my mom balloons
good morning aunt
morning my dear
morning Elmas
morning
you seem very happy
the wheather is really nice today
come on to the breakfast
aunt?
what happened you face
nothing big
he is beating you up!
my skin is so sensitive so it leaves a mark
aunt.its obvious he is beating you up
be quiet.its okay
im getting late i wont be able to eat
oh nur
this is my work car there is the address on it
stop by after you look for a job okay?we can come to home together
Elmas?
are you blind?
dont you see your mom's face
Nur dont make a big deal
your dada beating up your mom
im not seeing it...okay?
im not seeing anything
you know why?
because i didn't choose my mom and dad
but i chose the life i want to live
in that life there is not such a thing like being poor
im not gonna waste my take what my dad doing on mom and cant deal mom's drama
im not gonna make my make up run in this hole
im going to work
you love ballons uh
aunt did you see our ballon tree ?
of course i did my little
what a nice surprise from your dad
we have send ballons to my mom together
next time no running around with naked feet,lets go to change our clothes
go to grandma now
handsome boy
so you asked him to forgive you huh Yigit?
i dont know you did good or not
after the roof now he is going on trees,hope he will not do it again
i talked with him and did a deal with him
where is Cahit
he left early to not get yelled from his boss
you dont think he run away from his wife's big mouth huh?
what do you think?
dont forget Nazan
the most that i cant stand of is being two faces
a face smiling at dinner,cant argue after the doors closed...no one but no one can wear a mask in my home.
what did i say to yigit now huh?
i just messed with him that's all...did i say something bad
he got upset because i said something about his son
because inside of him he knows that he is spoiling too much
he is trying to be mom and dad at the same time.what he should do
his mom?really?since when Iclal was a mother of him
oh no being pregnant messed up my body,if i dont feed him from my breast the will hang down.or he got away from me after i gave him a baby.
saying stuff like this
what happened you became quiet?you cant say anything because im right
you aunt is burned your brother's head with her own daughter
just because te goods wont go to someone else,she forced them to get marry
you she she couldn't enjoy the rich life,its karma
anyways dont make me start now
iclal wasn't a good mother anyway
my daughter isn't dead Nazan...
My Iclal isn't dead
did you forget
isn't dead yet!
no one saw you right?
see that's how much im sure
auntie
you dont have to close your eyes for this
this guy can not do that to you
bring me a tea
what kind of man are you ?
Hafize,what is she talking about?
look at my aunt face
dont even try to raise your hand on her get that?
dont !dont even try!
Tayyar!
im sorry about family stuff
as you see
she wasn't polite to her elders
what do you think you are doing huh
in my land you cant raise your hand to a woman understand
i get it Mr
next time if see your hand in the air,you know what i would do right?
yes i do Mr
get lost
okay
Nur
Nur wait
you okay?
i was okay till you came...i can manage my own problems
you didn't need to show off
that wasn't show off
just talked to same language with him
and i did that for me not for you
by the way
balloon tree idea was really good
his laugh was all the way to my room
thank you
for the last night
and for the balloon tree
you are thanking me for balloon tree?
you made that tree to survive to be alive
my aunt wanted something from kitchen
i need to get them
you brother made me worse than kicking me out
on top of that,i have been slapped by your aunt at this age
nazan,
be calm i will talk to her
i wont let her if she raises her hand on you
yeah right they need to get permission from you right?
im done i wont even stay in this house another minute
nazan,
just me calk please lets talk about this when i get home
you still want to talk to me after all that
you come here be a man enough to protect your wife
Cahit,you down worry
whatever happened,its between us
you keep up with work work
dont get tired of our own problems
my love got stuck between two witch?
Elmas watch your mouth
how many time i told you to not stay next time when i talk something private on the phone,please
pardon me,Mr Cahit
as your hubby,i passed the limit i think
elmas.
i didn't mean that
okay i got it
i didn't come here to listen your phone
you wanted me to remind you that little issue
you said you were gonna buy the jewelry that you got for Nazan
dont buy it from the same store okay?
i love the way you get scared of your wife
dont worry i will go to the other store
im not a slave of this house Ms Aytul
if you keep going with this mental you will get more slaps
but not from me.from the life itself,
next time,if you call my daughter's name again from your mouth.
you wont even have a chance to pack up your luggage
and you will be out
lets see what you put in there
look at these
what ever we gave you in your wedding,you are taking them with you huh?
what you doin
i told you since you play the games between two brothers
one day in this house
if you gonna be out of the house,
you will be out with nothing,just like how you got in this house Nazan
this is my last warning,dont try to separate the nail from the finger.
be polite and remember that your are wife in to this house
otherwise i will burn your life
Cahit
can you come to my room
i need to talk with you
i broke your heart when i was mad about that tree
i did bad,forgive me
but you know me too
when i get mad i get black out
no worries Yigit
we know eachother
you are right
but
farm, business,business,mert,hospital all that
i forget everything
but i need to remember sometimes
what
that we are siblings?
look,its been so long that we haven't went aout together
do you have any plans this evening?
lets go to the restaurant lets drink and talk
good
lets go
see you in the evening
the bus arrives at pass 30 right?
you have go the town huh?
okay then fine look for job will evening
and then find Elmas to come together
where is cacao?
look at me,you dont even have cellphone
dont make me wonder okay?
okay aunt
where is Betul his milk is getting cold
that's okay i will take it to him
okay you do it then
where are you going,you dont even know his room yet
go upstairs the first room on front of you
don hang around too much Ms Aytul hates when people around
you okay?
why are you crying
i forgot the give my dad my drawing today
my sweetie you shouldn't cry for it
listen what i will tell you.i will go to see Elmas today.if you like i can take it your your dad.
can you really do that?
of course
but one condition
first wipe off your eyes
also you need to drink you milk
okay?
give me 22
Mr yigit there are some hearings about our fleet
our offer may be speculated
it would be good to guard them
let them do whatever they want
no one can draw my route with those losers
i also heard something too
there is something serious franchising about fleet business
they think they are discomforted by you
what you want me to suggest?
i mean,we should watch out
watch out? huh
just because of couple losers,we should watch out huh?
if they think my arms are on all over,let them come front of me and we can arm wrestle
if he stronger,he will win
if not,this is my battle..i cant be watching out
Muslum,crank it
let me hear the motor
Vural, what does the computer say now?
the code has been one Mr Yigit.
see..
it wasn't Transmission
shot the motor down...the problem was only few bolts...call the owner tell him the car is ready
his wife ate my brain last three days
that's all now,take it easy guys
after 10 minutes,lets look up those new models okay?
Mr yigit photoshoot has been started at the showroom
that's nice,you go there and let me know if anything goes wrong
10 minutes
the models we were suppose to look?
ah you are right
totally forgot
coming there in two minutes
good afternoon,im ooking for Elmas Celebi.im her cousin,Nur
one sec
is Elmas there?her cousin is here
okay
she is gone
okay thank you
if i leave you something would you give it to Yigit Kozan?
sure i can give it to his secretary
thank you
yes Mr yigit.
tell Nur to come my room
pardon miss
Mr Yigit want to see you
see me?but i didn't come her for him
come in please
have a seat he will be here shortly
i..was hanging the drawing...he are forgot to get it from your son today
Mert sent it with me
this door is always remains closed
it was opened when i got here
after i saw drawing on the wall...
im sorry
alright lets go
i dont get it.
aren't you here to see elmas?to go home
as you know Elmas isn't here,and we are going to same home
you are very polite Mr Yigit.
how do you know im going back to home?
i cant go back home myself?
im also turist in Istanbul.i was gonna ask her to be my tour guide today.
nice
lets go out then
i think you didn't understand
im not going home
Mr Yigit pardon.i was gonna talk about tomorrow's meeting...
tomorrow!
Mr yigit the faxes you wanted...
sign them.
can i get my backpack?
where are we going?
didn't you say that you are turist?let me show you istanbul
now you are telling me to show you to show are Istanbul? seriously?
serious
it was my last trip with my family in the Istanbul evening
after he came back,my mom got sick
my dad wanted to come here after he got sick last month
he didn't say it loud but...
may be it was because of this was the last place to smile for us
i found this in the garden this morning?
i cant believe this,i tought i lost it
thank you so much!
no problem
you look alike your mom
i mean i did look at the photo inside
want me to help you?
you loved ones you loved ones...right here!
we are not loved
here you go express photo
thank you
but we are not loved
what a nice what a nice
look at me boy.if you ever see a girl gets red face like her when talking about love just take her dont miss her
ok uncle you saying right but we are not in love eachother.how did you come up with that? does it say on our foreheads?
sonny this is love.it may say on your forehead or it may brighten up in your eyes
that brightness is the flash on your camera
we are not like loved ones
i didn't say that you guys are found eachother,i just said that you guys are fall in love...
keep the change
god bless you son
take it easy uncle thanks
here you go,a memory of istanbul
we look ugly
what if she got lost?what something happens her?
in a big istanbul
how did i let her go without cellphone
you think she would stay if you wouldn't let her go?
please stop Tayyar when did she disrespect us?
yesterday was the first against me and today is the second..she is out on the street at this time
she is looking for a job?she came here to hang around
you are so bad
what do you think you are doing huh?
im driving a car dont you see it!
i..i apologize
i was just joking
im sorry...
i just dont like a joke behind the wheel...its very dangerous
were you driving the car when you wife had a traffic accident?
im sorry again
forgive me
ok ok Cahit,i get it
do whatever you guys want to do
i dont know since when two brothers wants to eat outside
its been so long that they haven't been out for a while...probably they will have a melancholy night
aunt.when am i gonna have melancholy night?
you grow up first then you can have that too
aunt you were quiet all day
im a little tired
Mert you dad wont come you know that,why are you looking out the window?
im not waiting for my dad,im waiting for Nur
who is Nur?
that girl a nephew of Hafize
she was gonna give my draw to my dad
what is that mean
she is out of every conversation
We should talk to Hafize that she should not be around here
i dont want foreign people in my home.she can only stay with hafize
i want her to be around! i really like Nur
she can come to my room
look at him
it was very nice day..
i really liked your Istanbul
thank you
Nur
Istanbul is more beautiful with you
look at me hafize sit down in home
please dont stop me tayyar i can sit down at home and wandering of her
girl!where have you been !?
im sorry aunt
look at me Miss Nur
this is not your own house
you cant come home whenever you want to
my dear dont respond to him please
is this a hotel?
im sorry uncle
there was a traffic
this is Istanbul dont ever do this again.otherwise i wont let you again
anyways
let go to eat dinner
let me take my backpackand then will be back
take this too my dear
everday fight everyday noise
yigit you listening
im listening,im sorry
nazan,aunt my feet going backwards
when ever i talk to Nazan something its on my tongue that i want to tell her to divorce but it doesn't happen that easy
also that evil thing i have done behind her
evil?
you?
on Nazan?
no way!
i cant do that right?
im always a good man right
i cant do that right?.even tough every two words of my wife is that im not a man.
i wouldn't listen evil right?even though i do,after all feeling regret what i did all my life
look at me Cahit,whatever the sh*t you are eating tell me or divorce her like a man
am i man? huh?
dont make me start now
im not gonna send her to her family after all time
its hard of course
its is Yigit,it is
you can even divorce your wife that she is sleeping for last three years
you didn't even love her one day
i did a love marriage.but yougot married,with my aunt's force.just because your brother wasn't the man enough to be in family.
i think im better than you now..
i even accepted to love her after her screaming yelling
look cahit.i never believed a love
love,i its something created for romantic movies
always thought that for people who has free time
would you wait for something you that you dont know its there?you wouldn't..
if i was believing that there is a love that exist before...
before?
why before?
before from the turist..
what turist?
Russian turist?
look Cahit
imagine a pair of green eyes,
on the same time you see the furious and love from the same eyes
you see no giving up from the same eyes
to fight
its something like...she make you to be in a peace,when she argues with you for a tree
Russian?
we drunk too much,lets go
excuse me!
its like i put this huge city in my heart
Yigit kozan is in my mind with his istanbul
yigit...
his looks
his smell
his smile
his words
Yigit Kozan
what did you do to me?!
when did you do this ?
wait Cahit for me
i can go myself
sure
yeah
love...
love is actually is a something you can hold in your hands in learned
in your body...
in every every single cell that makes you to feel it
the love that always said never exist.its now something real like a blood circulating in my vein..
betul so sick today
maybe you should take upstairs the milk with cookies?
Nur.talking to you
okay i can take them to him my aunt
look at me dont hang around too much like how you did yesterday okay?
alright
make me fly my horse
good morning little man
hey..why didn't you come yesterday evening?
i couldn't make it but i kept my word and gave my draw to your dad yesterday
the photo you are looking is belong to my mom
she is very beautiful
sky huh?you like clouds ?
its not sky its heaven
and i dont like clouds at all because they are hiding my mom from me...one day she will be back
the clouds will let my mom go and then maybe i can be okay with them
do you know how's heaven look like
you just said it
like a sky
limitless
infinity
blue color?
i dont know may be
or maybe the color we have never seen it
im gonna find out anyways when my mom comes back
promise i will tell you too
do you know that my mom and dad in the heaven too
together?
dont be say my mom will bring them with her
what are you doing in here?
i brought him his milk and cookies
but its not your job
daddy grandma got mad at Nur
what happened aunt
this is not your home miss...you cant just walk the way you like to
if you are talking about that Nur spending time with Mert...
then im very happy
what is that mean Yigit?
Yigit could you let me go?i have to go
Mert,son
go to the backyard with Nur and wait for me there
run
whats going on?
you thought that she is nanny?
Mert liked her.
a girl that two days has been asking to help her stay in our facility...we dont even know her she is safe or not
also
since yesterday she is walking around home in silence
that what i always hated
im very happy that Mert spends time with Nur.period
look how im walking...hold my hand tight
iam dont worry
my mom would get mad at me if she see me like this
what about your grandma?
do you know who is my grandma?
she is my dad's aunt and also my grandma
she is always angry person.you dont be sad
she cant get mad at my dad,you know?no one can.
why nobody can get mad at your dad?
because he is super
look.you superman coming towards here
daddy
are we going to the fares?
of course
tell Nur to come with us
im sorry little man..you have fun
but its not fun with my dad
really now?
why not?
just because he doesn't want to ruin his charisma he doesn't get on carousel
he always winnin me on bumper cars
if you come we can be them against him
and we can win him
i really cant come,Mert
daddy what she saying
son,you go to the car
wait for us
Mr Yigit,i probably wasn't clear enough
you are still using 'we' word..im saying that i have things to do
dont you see that he want you to be with him
dont make him sad
this time im not accepting your force
you mad at me?
no im not
i should have thank you for your one more time being a hero for me right?
first you are not looking my face and then you being a lawyer of me against you aunt.right?
i didn't know that you did a marriage with your relative
anyways
im asking you...whats going on?
are you always talking like this?
yes
nice.just like me...good
im gonna talk like you too then
lets go you are coming with us
what are you doing?are you sick in the head?
didn't you realized that im not sick yet
what am i gonna say to my aunt?
you gonna tell her that Yigit is with me
im not getting order from you Mr Yigit.
everyone gets order by me but you dont get yet
you just get order from this little guy okay?
here we go another crazy person
did you just get mad at my dad?
no my dear
who can get mad at superman
i saw that you was successfully got mad at my dad
you not coming right?
he will lose the game by faking it
im coming
just because to win your dad
ok son its over...did you like it?
i did but.today better
for me too
come on get ready sleep time now
what happened son?
i feel shame of my mom..
why?
because i laughed so much today
what if mom sees me from there and what if she is sad
what if she thinks that i dont miss her anymore?
what if she doesn't back back because of this reason?
mothers are never get mad to their kids,son...
mothers always want their kid to be happy
they would want their kid to be sad
okay?
that's great then...so my mom laughed as much as i did then
of course she did
im so thankful that Nur was there too
she is my best friend from now.
she wouldn't ever leave us right?
she wouldnt
promise
what is this crazy guy doing on me?
one days he show me around istanbul
and then he changes his way after seeing me
i couldn't fall a sleep
i ended up being here after walking around
i come here to when i cant sleep
you doing good
good night
nur
dont go
what are you doing to me Yigit Kozan?
what is your problem with me?
what do you want from me?
since i saw you
one day you lifting up my feet
other day you putting me in the ground
one day when i look at your eyes,i see myself
other day the eyes that was looking at me is blind
what how i am
one day i wouldn't see anything but you
other day i would look in to you face
that's me
dont judge me the way iam from outside of me
whatever i did in this world was with a single  courage
but when i come front of you afraid helpless person i become
i need to run away from you Nur
understand?
brave is you,chicken is you two of them is you
i accept both
im fine with which
ever runs away
but let one stay
with me
something happened me
first time...in my life
when i saw you something happened me
Yigit im afraid too
more than being afraid
freaking out
whatever happened to you,happened to me too
im fall in love with you
im fall in love with you too
are we gonna have to hide us from people?
sometimes when i look at my aunt and elmas i get afraid..if they find out that i love you.
i wan to share my happiness with them
and then
my dad comes to my mind
it didn't even past 40 days since he is gone
the happiness that lifts up my feet from the ground,that was not in a good time
bad timing...you are right
the love has arrived in a very bad time
it got us very quick suddenly
we dont want anyone find out
one day everyone will find out
ah! silly you!
come here!
look at me,Yigit Kozan he became lamb chaser
are you complaining?
sweetie. you have left without your mommy?
i love you!
i love you too!
lets go
our little kid is gonna get crazy after seeing this
our?
i mean,yours...Mert
our kid...you really love Mert
of course i do...i wish i can do more for him
i haven't asked you before but very curious
did you ever take Mert to pedagogue?
reason?
you son still waiting his dead mom to be back
he is confused about being a death
he thinks people will come back after they are dead
isn't this enough reason?
Mert is still little
not so little to not understand death
also
why he isn't in the school?why you guys getting report for him?
lookyour son should not live like this
i wouldn't want to make you sad but you sould realize this
this is too much for a little kid
how are you gonna know what is a heavy stuff for my kid?im doing everthing to take all the waights on him
get it?
no
i really try to but i cant understand you
where is his mom's rest?
did he ever go to her rest?
no right?
i knew this
look
im not a psychologist
but all he needs is that..
a real parting with her
if you give him this,
enough!
my his dad understand
im his dad
who are you?huh?
i can only know th best for my son
his mom and her rest  are nothing your business
god damn me!
you animal!
daddy
look i brought you a new friend
did you get this for me?
yeah i did,so you can stop playing with chickens
that's the only thing we needed
dad she didn't like my sheep at all
i love you more than myself Yigit
even though i know that you never did love me
i want to live th rest of my love even for one day you would love me
there is no such as chance Iclal
i dont believe the love you have
you dont believe love Yigit?
i believe the logic,and realistics thing Iclal
like my aunt says
its good to be together
two right person.is good to be together
you dont love me you don see me
im driying out with you love in this home
im disappearing more everyday you dont love me,dont you see it?
i never gave you hope for love
you killing me by not loving me
look iclal i want to divorce with you
im sorry Iclal
that i didn't love you
that i couldn't love you for everyday
Mr ihsan
hello! i have very important thing that we need to get it done
i would like to diverce from my wife that has been in a vegetable life for 3 years
its more painful for you than being her over here
she is just sleeping with seeinf dreams
i hope she doesn't have kid...her husband is not coming to visit too often...
im ordering you to change Iclal's nurse
did anything go wrong ?
im not happy with her service
im at the hospital
where did you say?
oh okay im nearby,coming there
i was thinking you would be in the office
i had to get things done
are you stressed?
something happened?
no,nothing
you just have to sign some paperwork
what are those?
some partnership paperwork at work
you need to sign them too
let me get my glasses,you know that i cant see close
you dont need to read aunt.its about the procedures at work
just sign it
yeah?fine
here?
this one too
here you go
you brought me here for only few papers?
im sorry that i took your time
we are in rush,thats why
we will go the greeting for Emre,can you make it?
of course
move away
where to?
going to town i have things to do
ok fine let me take you
what
why did you react like this?im just telling you take you to there
you dont understang i have things to do
would you get in or should i make you to?
okay im listening
im sorry Nur i apologize
you borught me here just to say sorry?if  i dont accept your sorry?
you broke my heart and will fit it now?
yes
whatever i said to you wasn't inside me
because of my fear
helpless?
you the one helpless?
what did i do to you?
what did i do to make you fear from me
you make me love you
im afraid
my love is rough because there are fear inside of it
i promise your life will be safe when you are with me
look at myself
im sad of you but i have no one else to complain you
look Nur right here and right now im gonna say this and just say yes okay?
marry me
this is crazy
yes this is crazy because you are the craziest thing i can ever have in this world
you still have chance to escape but if you ever say yes,
yes!yes!
i have no other option to get away from you Yigit
i love you like a man can you his woman in most
i love you
everytime i look at you
did he sleep?
yes he did
first he kept wanting his lamb but after reading him a story he slept
i have been noticing that you phone down go down from you hand?
come on brother
let her be she is young
where is Yigit
i dont like the was he is these days
is everything is good at work Cahit?
i dont think something is wrong aunt
d you sign those paperwork too?
what paperwork?
i dont know what paperwork,he said something about small
yigit,yigit stop
how didn't we think about nothing to get it like this
what we gonna tell people right now
eveone will be shocked
what about Mert? what if he starts to have more?
okay relax
i dont have anyone else to explain this in this house
brother
Yaren tell us what happened.dont scare us
he got married
brother what did you do?
after my wife kisses my aunt hand,i will explain to you guys
what wife?
shame on you
aunt i will talk to you guys
shut up
if i die over here you will be the reason
come nur let me take you to the room
sit down my love
its my fault
i should have talk to them first
i will talk to them and then i will talk to you
i need you to know something very important
trust me
im trusting you
brother did you lose your mind?
weren't you married already
you be quiet
i would want it to be like this
but it happened
i have no other option
now listen me guys
you...
you fooled me
you made me to sign that paperwork to divorce her
you divorced my daughter with my opportunity
i wasn't only a half mother for you,i was a full of mother foryou
i was a father for you too
but what you did?
you divorced my daughter
with a maid of this house
i have nothing else to tell you
shame on you!
enough!!
i loved her
and married her
nur is my wife
my wife
either you guys freak out or break  things up do whatever you guys want
she will be my wife
you guys will need to accept this
mr yigit? surprise! your wife opened her eyes! can you hear me? hello?