Good job.
Did we make up?
We did.
Listen, son.
Wherever you go from now on
to the trees, to the clouds, to the sun
wherever you go, don't ever let go of dad's hand. Got it?
-Got it. -Good boy.
Let's wave to my mom, dad.
Dad, should we send a balloon to my mom?
Let's do it.
Here.
Wait.
Let's count to three and let go together, ok?
One, two, three.
Balloons, go greet my mom.
-Good morning, aunt. -Good morning, dear.
Good morning, Elmas.
Good morning.
What's up? You seem very happy.
The weather outside is beautiful today.
-Come eat breakfast, my dears. -Come on.
Aunt?
What happened to your face?
Nothing, my dear.
Aunt, look at me.
My uncle is beauting you?!
Shh! It's alright, Nur. It was just a slap
My face is very sensible. It leaves a mark right away.
Aunt, it's clear!
-He is beating you! -Shh. It's ok.
I am getting late, I won't eat,
I will be leaving right away. Oh, Nur!
This is my company's card. The address is on there.
Stop by after you are done searching for a job. We can go home together.
Elmas.
Are you blind?
Are you deaf? Can't you speak?
Don't you see the state your mom is in?
Nur, my dear. Don't make a fuss.
Your dad is beating your mom!
Can't you see, Elmas?
I don't. Do you understand, Nur?
I don't see anything.
You wanna know why?
Because I didn't choose these parents.
But I did choose the life I wanna live!
In this life there is no room for this misery.
I don't have time to waste for my father's torments or my mother's wretchedness.
I don't plan to let my mascara run down in a place like this.
I am going to work.
You really do love balloons, don't you?
Aunt, did you see our balloon tree?
How could I not? I did. What a wonderful surprise of your dad.
We let balloons fly for my mom together.
Don't run around bare foot. Come here, let's dress you.
Go on to grandma. Come on. Time to dress.
Handsome.
So you did ask for forgiveness because of yesterday, didn't you, Yigit?
Though I don't know if you did the right thing.
Now that he is done with the roof, I hope he doesn't make a thing of climbing trees.
I did talk to my son. We made a deal.
Where is Cahit? Did he leave already?
He left early to avoid getting scolded by his boss.
You don't think he left early to get away from his wife?
No?
Don't forget, Nazan.
One thing I can tolerate the least in this world are two-faced people.
You cannot talk bad behind closed doors.
No one in my house, NO ONE
can run around wearing masks.
What did I say just now to Yigit, huh?
I was just messing around. Did I say something bad?
My, he got upset just because I said something regarding his son.
Because deep down he knows himself, that he spoiled him too much.
He is trying to fill the hole his mom left behind, what is he supposed to do?
The hole his mom left?
Please. Someone who hears you might think, that Iclal ever was a mother to that child. What did she ever do?
Her whole purpose was to run after Yigit
and cry about how her pregnancy ruined her body, and how if she breastfeeds it might get saggy,
and how her husband distanced herself since she gave birth.
What's up? You got all quiet. Of course, you cannot agree, out of fear of your aunt.
That aunt, that aunt.
She did ruin your brother with her own daughter basically.
'Aunt', what a joke.
Sister(-in-law)....
Just to keep the wealth in the family, she has thrown her own daughter at her nephew.
But see what has happened? Mrs Iclal couldn't even taste the wealth.
Please, Yaren. Don't make me talk.
As if Iclal was a mother when she was alive.
When a blind person dies they are remembered with almond eyes. (Proverb: People are seen in a better light after their death)
My daughter isn't dead, Nazan.
My Iclal is not dead.
Not dead.
No one did see you, you are sure, right?
That's how sure I am.
Aunt.
You don't have to bear this.
This man can not treat you like this.
Bring me a tea.
What kind of man are you?!
-Nur, my child! -Hafize,
What does this rude one talk about?
Look at my aunt's face.
You won't raise your hand ever again, do you understand?!
You won't touch my aunt ever again.
-Are you trying to scold me, you shameless?! -Oh my!
Don't. Don't, uncle.
Tayyar!
I am sorry, Mister Yigit. It's a family matter.
You have seen it yourself.
A bad behaved, rude girl. She is driving one crazy.
What do you think you are doing? What do you think you are doing?!!
You cannot raise your hand against a woman on my land! Do you understand?
I understand, Mister Yigit.
If I ever see your hand raised like that, you know what I will do, don't you?
-I know. -You know, don't you? -I know.
Leave.
-Yes, Sir. -Leave! I don't want to see you.
Nur.
Wait.
Are you alright?
I was good even before you came.
I did solve my problem myself.
You didn't need to show off like that.
It was not a show off.
I just talked in a language your uncle understands.
And not for you, but for myself.
By the way, the balloon tree was a good idea.
I could hear the laughs of the little one way back in my room.
Thank you.
For last night.
And for the balloon tree.
You thank me for the balloon tree?
Well, you kept that tree alive.
My aunt asked for something from the kitchen, so I should go.
Your little brother did worse than kick me out.
And on top of that, I did get a slap from your aunt at my age.
Nazan.
It's okay. Please calm down. I will talk to my aunt.
I won't allow her raise her hand against you.
Yeah, because they will ask you to allow them, right?
Because they were supposed to ask for your permission, right?
What does it matter if you let them or not?
That's enough. I won't stay in this house one more minute.
Nazan.
Please be calm. We can talk when I am home.
You still want to talk to me after all that?!
Come here, be a man and take care of your woman.
If you talk to your little brother, or to your aunt-
Cahit, don't bring yourself down.
Whatever happened is between your wife and me.
We both talk in a language we understand.
Go back to your work. Don't bother with our problems.
Is my lover stuck between two witches?
Elmas, please watch your mouth.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't stay next to me when I talk about personal things.
Sorry, Mister Cahit.
Seems like I have crossed a line as your mistress.
Elmas, I didn't mean it like that.
I-It's just...
Yeah, nevermind. Don't start to stutter right away.
I didn't come here to hear you talk anyway.
There was a small thing, that you wanted me to remind you.
You said you wanted me to buy the same jewelry you bought Mrs Nazan.
But don't buy from the same place, okay?
I love your cowardness.
Don't worry, I will go to another store.
I am not the whipping boy of this house, Mrs Aytul.
If you keep going like this, you will have a lot of beatings.
But not from me. From life itself.
If I ever hear the name of my daughter coming out of that sinister mouth of yours,
if you ever slander my daughter again,
you won't even have the chance to pack your things, before you end up through that door.
Let's see what you packed in that suitcase.
-Mrs Aytul! -Shh.
Look at that.
You are taking all we gave you for your wedding.
What are you doing, Mrs Aytul?
I told you the first day when you tried to pit those two brothers against each other
one day if you leave this house
you will leave the way you came in as a bride, as 'tatters-wearing Nazan'.
Nazan, that's my last warning for you.
Don't try to separate what's blood and flesh.
Be well-behaved. Know you are a bride in this house.
Or else I am gonna hurt you really bad.
Really bad.
Cahit.
Can you come into my room? I want to talk with you about something.
So, Cahit...
I broke your heart with that tree issue yesterday.
I was being dumb. Please forgive me.
But you also know me.
I get blind with rage.
It's no matter, Yigit. We know each other.
It's true. It's true, but...
Well, with the farm, the company, work, Mert,
hospital and all, I tend to forget everything.
But one has to remember once in a while.
What? That we are big brothers and little brother?
Listen. You and I didn't get to spend time together for some time now.
Do you have work tonight?
-Let's do something together. -Fine for me.
Let's do that. I'll see you tonight.
The bus arrives at past 30 right.
So you really want to go down to the city?
Then do that, and search for a job till evening.
And then find Elmas and come back together. Where is the cacao?
Listen, you don't even have a phone.
Don't make me worry, okay?
Of course, aunt.
Where is Betül? The child's milk is getting cold.
It's alright, aunt. I can bring it to him.
Do that.
Where are you going? You don't even know where his room is?
Up the stairs, first room in front.
Don't take too much time. Mrs Aytul doesn't like people walking around.
Okay.
Mert?
Mert.
Are you okay?
Why are you crying?
I wanted to give a drawing to my dad.
I forgot.
My sweetie, is that a reason to cry?
Listen.
I will be going to Sister Elmas' workplace today.
If you want to I can bring your drawing to your dad.
Would you do that for me?
Of course.
But under one condition.
First you wipe away your tears
and if you take a big sip of your milk
I will bring it to him. Deal?
Deal.
Let's go.
Here.
Give me the twenty-two.
Mister Yigit, there are some rumors regarding the Filo family?
I think they are going to speculate over our offer.
It would be good to be careful.
They should not take everything for granted.
A few rumors of cowards won't keep me from going my way.
Yigit, I also heard a few things this morning.
There is a serious monopolization going on with the Filo business, you know that.
They seem to be bothered. They think you are reaching out for too much.
What do you suggest? Twenty-four.
I think we should be more cautious.
Cautious?
Cautious, huh?
Just because some tires manufacturer cowards are scared of competition, we should watch out?
If someone thinks I am reaching out for too much
he should come in front of me, grab my hand and arm wrestle.
If he is stronger he will win.
If not...
that's what competition means to me.
I won't be cautious.
Muslum, start the car. I want to hear the motor.
Vural,
what does the computer say?
The fault recording system is clear now, Mister Yigit.
See? It wasn't the transmission.
It was three, four screws, wasn't it?
Stop the motor.
Call the owner to pick it up.
He is waiting for 3 days. His wife was driving me crazy.
Well, that's all.
Take it easy, guys.
In 10 minutes let's take a look at the new models together, okay?
Mister Yigit, the photoshoot in the gallery has started.
Great. You go there.
If there is a problem tell me, okay?
-Of course. -10 minutes.
You said we wanted to look at the models.
Ah, yes.
I must have forgotten. I am coming.
Give me two minutes.
Good afternoon. I was looking for Elmas Celebi. I am her cousin, Nur.
One second.
Is Miss Elmas at her desk? Her cousin is here.
Okay.
-Miss Elmas left. -I see. Thank you.
If I gave you something, could you give it to Yigit Kozan?
Of course. I can give it to his secretary.
Thank you.
Yes, Mister Yigit.
-Send Miss Nur to my office immediately. -Yes, Sir.
Excuse me. Mister Yigit wants to see you.
Me?
I am not here for him.
Please follow me.
Here. Please take a seat, he will be here any moment.
I was hanging up the drawing.
You forgot to take it. It's from Mert.
This door is always closed.
When I came the door was open.
And when I saw the drawings...
I am sorry.
Well.
Let's go out.
I don't understand.
Are you not here to meet with Elmas?
To go home?
If you didn't notice, Elmas isn't here. And we live in the same place.
Come on.
A really polite order, Mister Yigit.
And how do you know I am going back home?
Can't I go home alone, or what?
Also I count as a tourist in Istanbul
and I wanted to be shown around by Elmas.
Great. Then let's go.
I think you didn't understand. I said I am not going home.
Excuse me, Mister Yigit. For tomorrow's meeting-
Tomorrow.
-Mister Yigit, the faxes you asked for. -Sign them.
Can I get my bag, please?
Where are we going?
Well, didn't you say you are a tourist?
Let me guide you through Istanbul.
Are you seriously gonna show me Istanbul now?
Seriously.
We had our last vacation as a family in Istanbul.
One month after coming back my mom god sick.
Past month when my father's condition worsened
he said he wanted to come here again.
He never said it out loud but
I think it was because it was the last place we were happy as a family.
I found this in the garden this morning.
I can't believe it.
I thought I'd lost it.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
You really look like your mother.
I mean...
I saw it by accident while inspecting.
Do you need help?
The ones being in love, the ones being in love!
This way! This way!
We are not in love.
Take this! Snap! Snap!
Thank you.
But we are not in love.
Very pretty. Very pretty.
Listen, young man.
In this time if you find a young girl who blushes when hearing about love,
don't ever lose her. Take her and never let go.
Well, uncle, it's true. But we are not in love.
How do you know? Is it written on our forehead?
My son, this is love.
It will be written on your forehead and sparkle in your eyes.
Are you sure it's not the flash of your camera?
We are not lovers.
I am not saying you have found each other.
I am saying you are in love.
Even so you are wrong...
take this money. Keep the change. Thank you.
God bless you. Thank you.
Take it easy, uncle. Thanks.
Here for you.
An Istanbul memory.
We look ugly.
What if she got lost?
What if something happened to her? It's huge Istanbul.
How could I send her without a phone?
As if she would have stayed.
You could tie her up, but she would still find a way, that disrespectful girl.
Don't be like this Mister Tayyar. When was she disrespectful?
First yesterday and today is the second time.
She is this late on the first day!
What was it? She is searching for a job?
She is here to party, your beloved niece. To party!
(sings along)
''Who do I have in Istanbul...?''
You are the worst.
Iclal, what are you doing?! Iclal!
What do you think you are doing?
What do you think you are doing?!
I'm driving, can't you see?
I- I am sorry. I...
-was just joki- -Sorry.
Sorry, I...
I just don't like joking around while driving.
It's very dangerous.
When your wife died in a car crash,...
where you the one driving?
I am sorry.
Forgive me.
I am really sorry.
Yes, okay, Cahit. I understand.
Do what you want.
Yigit and Cahit are gonna eat out today, wherever{ that came from.
They weren't going out for a while now.
They will probably have a night of (heavy drinking).
Aunt, I also want a night of (heavy drinking).
First of all grow up, then you can have your night outs.
Aunt, you are quite today.
I am a little tired.
Mert, you know your father won't come tonight. Why are you watching the window?
I am not waiting for dad, I am waiting for Nur.
Who is Nur?
The niece of Mrs Hafize.
She was supposed to give dad my picture.
What do you mean?
She is everywhere to be found.
Once in the car, Once on the tree. She was very excited to be inside the house.
She had a weird way of looking at the rooms and the furniture.
She has a pretty sly and swagger persona.
One must have a talk with Mrs Hafize.
If she came to stay in the outbuilding, she should stay there.
I don't want a stranger like her to linger in the house.
I want that! I love Nur a lot!
I don't care! I want her to come!
This boy...
It was a very nice day.
I liked Yigit Kozan's Istanbul a lot.
Thank you.
Nur.
Istanbul was prettier with you.
Listen, Hafize.
Sit down for once. Don't make me break your legs.
For the love of God, please don't stop me. I can't stay here, all worried...
Hafize!
Girl, where were you?!
I'm sorry, aunt.
Listen to me, Miss Nur.
This is not your father's house.
You can't just stay out how you like and come home at this late hour. Got it?
-(whispers)Don't... -Is this a hotel?! Is this a hotel?!
I am sorry, uncle. I was stuck in traffic.
My God...
You can't just do that to me, Girl. This is Istanbul.
I won't let you go out if that happens again.
Whatever... Let's eat dinner.
Aunt, I'll just drop my bag upstairs real quick.
-Can you take this, too? -Sure.
Go out of my way!
Fights every day, a fuss everyday.
Yigit, do you listen?
I'm listening. I'm listening. Sorry.
Nazan here, my aunt there,...
I never feel like going home.
Sometimes when I talk to Nazan, I get so close to asking for divorce, but...
I can't.
And then there is this guilt, because of that Devil...
-Devil?
Devil.  The tempting charming devil. [He is hinting on an affair.]
You?
You...? On Nazan?
No way.
I wouldn't, would I? I am always the nice guy.
Even though my wife is asking 'Are you a man?' every other sentence...
I would never fall for the devil.
And If I had fallen, I would be caught in guilt like this.
Look at me, Cahit.
If you are a ******, just admit it like a man.
Or divorce like a man.
Am I a man, huh?
Come on.
Don't make me talk now.
Even if it's hard sometimes, it's been so many years
I can't divorce her after all this time and send her back to her family home.
Yeah, it surely is difficult.
It's difficult, Yigit, so difficult.
Look at you.
You couldn't even divorce your wife who is asleep for 3 years.
You didn't love her even for a day.
I even married while being in love. A marriage out of love.
You... got pressured by our aunt.
Because your big brother couldn't produce a successor for the big Kozans Family.
I got more luck than you did...
I even fell in love with my wife's never ending chatter.
Listen, Cahit. I didn't believe in love.
Love...
... how do I say it...
...is made up by romance movies.
Like something that people with free time use to feel better about themselves.
Would you wait for a feeling you believe to not exist?
You wouldn't wait.
But before that...
had I believed in love just for a second....
'Before'?
Before what?
Before the tourist.
What tourist?
Is she a russian?
Listen, Cahit.
Imagine a pair of green eyes.
In those same eyes...
you see someone who challenges everyone and everything...
but also you see compassion.
You see the urge to stand one's ground, in those eyes... in her face.
Not to give up. To fight.
It's such a thing that...
even if she fights with you because of a tree,...
she helps you to make peace with yourself.
Is it a russian?
You *****, let's go.
Excuse me.
It felt like I have placed a huge city inside my heart today.
Yigit Kozan's Istanbul lives inside of me.
Yigit. His glances.
His smell.
His laugh.
His words.
Yigit Kozan, what have you done to me?
When did you do it?
Wait, Cahit. Wait.
Wait, Cahit.
Ok, ok.
I am not drunk, I can go on my own.
-Are you sure? -Yes.
Drink a soda and Ayran[turkish drink made of yoghurt], it will help.
Love...
Love is actually something you can grasp with your hands.
In your body. Something you can feel in every part of you.
Like the cramps in your belly.
Like the cold sweat you feel on your body whenever you see them.
The love, I believed to be non-existent for years,...
is just as real as the blood that flows through my veins.
But while the blood that flows through my veins keeps me alive,
this kills me.
Betül is still sick with the flu.
Would you bring this milk and cookies to Mert?
Nur, I am talking to you.
Would you bring this milk with cookies to Mert?
Sure, Aunt.
But don't get distracted like yesterday!
Yes.
Come on, my horse!
Fly me away, fly me to the sky!
Come on, my flying horse! Fly!
Good morning, little man.
Hey! Why didn't you come yesterday?
I couldn't. But I did keep my promise.
I did give the picture to your dad.
Yey!
The picture you are looking at is my mother's.
She's very pretty.
The sky, huh?
You like the clouds?
That's not the sky. That's heaven.
And I don't like the clouds at all.
Because they hide my mother.
But one day she will come back.
The clouds will let my mother go.
Maybe then I can make peace with the clouds.
What do you think is heaven like?
You said it already.
Like the sky.
Without things to hold you down. Infinite.
Is it blue?
I don't know.
Maybe it's blue.
Or maybe it's in colors we have never seen.
I will know what kind of place it is anyways.
When my mom comes back, she is going to tell me.
I am going to tell you after, I promise.
Did you know...
my mother and father are also in heaven.
-Both at the same time? -Yeah.
Don't be sad. When my mom comes back, she can bring them along, too.
What are you doing here?
I brought milk and cookies for Mert.
This is not your job.
Dad, grandma got angry at Nur.
What's wrong, Aunt?
-I should-      -This is not your home, little Miss.
You can't just walk around the rooms as you please.
If you are talking about the fact that Nur spends time with Mert...
I am very pleased with that.
What is that supposed to mean, Yigit?
Do we need a stranger to take care of Mert?