Mr Yigit, could you please go out of my way. I want to leave.
Mert. My son.
Go downstairs with Nur.
Wait for me in the garden.
Hurry up.
What's happening, Yigit? Did you think this girl is a babysitter?
Mert likes the girl.
It's a girl who is staying in the outbuilding for 2 days now.
We don't know her.
Why should she take care of Mert?!
Also she is quietly sneaking around the house since yesterday.
Something I don't like at all.
I am very pleased that Nur spends time with Mert.
I am done. That's all.
Look how I walk. You won't let go, will you?
I am holding you tight, don't worry.
My grandma would be mad if she saw us.
Grandma?
Did you know who my grandma is?
He is the aunt of my father and also the mother of my mom.
She is always angry, don't be sad about it.
She can't get angry at my dad only.
Did you know? Noone can be angry at my dad.
Why can't noone be angry at your dad?
Because he is super!
Look, there he comes, your Superman.
Dad!
Dad, can we go to the amusement park?
We can. I promised you, didn't I?
Yey! Nur should come, too!
I am sorry, little man, U can't. I wish you a lot of fun.
But it's no fun with my dad.
Sorry?
Why is that?
My dad doesn't even ride the carousel with me, because he is scared he might lose his charisma.
He always let's me win at the electric cars, because he knows I can't win on my own.
If you come, we can be a team and win against him.
I really can't go, Mert.
Dad, what is she saying?
Son, you go run to the car.
Go, wait for us. Come on.
Mr Yigit, maybe I couldn't make myself clear.
You still say 'us'. I say I have things to do.
Can't you see, the kid really wants you.
Don't make him sad.
This time I won't listen to your orders.
Are you mad at me?
No. I am not mad.
I should be thankful for your last heroic action.
I am so ungrateful again.
First you don't look at me.
And then you play lawyer infront of your mother-in-law, your aunt, for me.
I didn't know you married a relative.
Whatever, I am asking you: What's going on?
Are you always so straight forward?
Yes.
Perfect. So just like me.
Nice, I will also be straight forward.
Come on, we are going.
What are you doing? Are you insane?
Didn't you get that I am insane yesterday already?
-I said, we are going. Come on. -What am I going to say to my aunt?
You will say 'It was Mr Yigit's orders', what else?
-I am not taking orders from you, Mr Yigit.
Everyone is taking orders from me, but you don't have to.
You take orders from that little man, can you?
----
Did you get angry at my dad a moment ago?
No way.
How dare I?
Who can get angry with Superman?
I've seen it. I did.
You did get angry with him.
You won't come with us, will you?
He is gonna lose on purpose at the cars again.
I am coming.
Just to win over your dad.
Hooray! Yey!
He turned yellow immediately.
And punished the trickster weavers.
So, son.
Another fairy tale is finished.
Did you like it?
I liked it, but
today was better.
Today was really great for me also.
It was nice, but
the amusement park was nice, too.
Come on, time to go to sleep.
Make yourself ready.
What's going on, child. Why do you get grumpy?
I am ashamed to face mother.
Why?
I laughed a lot, that's why.
What if mother sees me from heaven and gets sad.
What if she thinks I don't miss her and that's why she isn't coming back.
Come here.
Mothers don't sulk about that.
Mothers always want their children to be happy.
They wouldn't want them to be sad.
Ok?
Hooray. That means mother probably just laughed as much as I did, today.
Surely.
Good that Nur came, too.
Nur is now my best friend.
She will never leave, right?
She won't leave.
I promise.
What does this silly man do to me?
One day he shows me Istanbul,
then he walks the other way when he sees me.
What does he do to me?
I couldn't sleep.
I walked around and ended up at the lake.
I also come to the lake when I can't sleep.
That's a good idea.
Good night.
Nur.
Don't leave.
What are you doing to me, Yigit Kozan?!
What's your problem with me?! What's your problem?!
What do you want from me?!
Since the first day I met you, what are you doing to me?!
One day you make me feel like I am flying,
the next day you bury me under the ground.
One day, I see myself in your eyes,
the next day, the eyes that look at me are blind.
What are you doing to me?!
I am this type of man.
One day, I don't see anything other than you,
the next day, I can't look you in the face.
That's the type of man I am.
Don't get fooled by my boldness.
Everything I have done in my life, I've done with a certain bravery.
But in front of you...
I turn into a weak and helpless coward.
I have to run away from you, Nur.
Do you understand?
I have to run away from you.
You are brave and you are a coward.
You are both.
And I accept both.
Who ever runs away, can run away.
But one should stay.
He should stay with me.
Something happened to me.
For the first time,
for the first time in my life,
something has happened to me when I saw you for the first time.
Yigit.
I am also afraid.
What is even 'afraid'?
I am terrified.
Because what ever happened to you
it also happened to me.
I have fallen in love with you.
I have fallen in love with you, too.
Yigit.
Will we have to hide like this for ever?
Sometimes when I look at my aunt's or Elmas' face, I'm scared.
Like it is written on my forehead, that I am in love with Yigit Kozan.
'I am in love with him infront of your eyes, can't you see?', is what I am thinking.
I want to share my happiness.
And then....
I remember my father.
He isn't even dead for 40 days,
and this happiness that has swept me off my feet,
at the wrong time
feels like too much.
At the wrong time?
Yes.
This love came at the wrong time.
We were caught to abruptly by this.
Without questions, without answers. From one day to another.
---------
We want no one to know, but
one day they all will.
Ah! A lamb!
So silly, look.
Come here!
Got'cha.
Loot at me.
The great Yigit Kozan is turned into a shepherd, thanks to you.
Are you complaining, 'great Yigit Kozan'?
Come here.
Aw, my love.
Are you without your mother?
Nur.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Let's go.
My dear.
My baby.
Our little one is gonna flip out.
Our?
I mean 'yours'. Mert.
Our...
You really love Mert.
How could I not?
I wish I could do more for him than this lamb, the games and the paintings.
Yigit.
I didn't ask you before, but I am very curious.
Have you ever brought Mert to a psychiatrist?
For what reason?
The reason?
Your son is still waiting for his dead mother...
I think he has wrong ideas about death.
He thinks that people can come back from heaven.
Is that not reason enough?
Mert is still very young.
He is not too young to understand death in a healthy way.
And...
why isn't Mert in school? Why did you get a doctors note?
Why doesn't he go to school?
Listen, your son can't live waiting for his mother.
Yigit, I don't want to upset you, but
you have to see that.
It's too much for a small child. It's too heavy for a burden.
How do you know what is a heavy burden and what not?
I do everything to make it easier for my son.
Everything. Do you understand?!
I don't.
I am really trying to understand, but I don't.
Yigit. My love.
Where is Mert's mother's grave?
Did Mert ever visit her grave?
He didn't, did he?
I thought so.
Listen, I am not a psychiatrist.
But the only thing Mert needs is to say good bye to his mother in a true way.
If you give him that and bring him to his mother's grave-
Enough!
I am Mert's parent. Do you get it?!
I am Mert's father!!
Who are you? Who are you?
I know what's the best, the healthiest and most right for my son.
His mother, nor his mother's grave, nor anything else regarding his mother,
has anything to do with you!
You piece of shit. You scumbag, asshole!
To whom am I even talking to?
Dad!
Look, I got you a new friend!
Come here, come here.
Dad, did you get a lamb?!
Yes, maybe now you will stop playing with the chickens for once.
We were only lacking of a lamb.
Nur, look at my lamb!
Come, let's pet it together.
He is super smart and calm.
Dad, Nur didn't like my lamb at all.
I love you more than myself, Yigit Kozan.
Even though I knew that you didn't love me
I want to spend the rest of my life believing that one day you will love me.
There is no chance that I will, Iclal.
I don't believe in that type of love.
Love.
Don't you believe in love?
I believe in the brain, the mind, and what is right.
Just like my aunt said,
that you and I are together is right, but two rights don't make a wrong.
We can marry.
You don't love me.
You don't even see me.
While you play with your son, your horses, your cars,
I rot away at this farm with nothing but my love for you.
Every day you don't love me, I wither away a little more.
I didn't promise you love.
I didn't promise that I will be in love with you.
You are killing me.
By not loving me, you are killing me.
Listen, Iclal. I want to divorce you.
Do you understand? I want to divorce you.
-You want to divorce me, is that right? -Yes.
-You want to build a life without me? -Yes.
But for me there is no life without you, Yigit.
If there is no you, then there is also no life.
I am sorry, Iclal.
I am sorry.
For every moment I haven't loved you,
for every moment I couldn't... I am sorry.
Hello Mr Isam, there is something important we need to take care of.
I need you to be really fast.
I want to divorce my wife,
who is in coma for 3 years.
The worry of the one who is on her feet is worse, than the one who is asleep.
While she's sleeping peacefully, dreaming,
you are the one who has to suffer.
Just imagining the pain of a mother like you are...
I hope there is no grandchild.
I believe her husband doesn't visit too often as well.
I want Iclal's nurse to be switched immediately.
Was there a problem, madam?
I am not happy with the nurse. I want it to be taken care of today.
Sure.
Yigit?
I am at the hospital.
Where did you say?
That's close anyway. I am on my way.
I thought you are at the company.
I had stuff to take care of.
Are you in a bad mood?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I am pretty well.
There are just a few documents you have to sign.
What are these?
Nothing. Just a few formalities regarding the company's stocks.
You have to sign, too.
Let me get my glasses. You know I can't see close up.
You don't have to read it, aunt. It's just simple formalities.
Just sign and forget it.
Yeah? Well.
Here.
Like this?
-Is this the same? -Yeah, all the same.
Here you go.
Did you make me rush here just for a few documents?
I am sorry for the trouble.
I really had to hurry with this.
That's all.
We will go greet Emir at the bus terminal in the evening. You will make it, right?
I will! I missed him like crazy.
Hello Mr Yigit.
Ah, Nur! Be here before 4pm, or else you won't find anyone home.
Nur.
-Out of my way. -Where are you going? -None of your business.
I said 'where'?
Down to the city. I have stuff to do.
Ok, let me drive you.
What?
Why are you so surprised? Jump in and I'll drive you.
It seems like you don't understand. I said I have stuff to do.
Will you get in the car on your own?
Or should I force you?
Here we are.
Speak. I am listening.
I am sorry, Nur.
I apologize.
You brought me all the way here just to apologize?
What are you going to do, if I don't forgive you? Tell me.
You broke my heart using force, are you going to heal it with force, too?
Yes.
I broke your heart using force.
I forced myself to break it.
But none of my words came from my soul.
It was out of fear.
Out of desperation.
Desperate? You are desperate?
What have I done to make you feel this way?
What have I done to make you so afraid?
You made me fall in love.
You made me fall in love, Nur.
I was scared. I am scared.
I know I will spend my life being scared of losing you.
Listen.
Come here.
Come, lay your head down.
Look.
My love is irritable and rough, because it is filled with fears.
Because we are inside.
I can't promise to never make you sad.
But I promise you,
as long as you are next to me,
this world will be a safer place for you.
Look at me.
I get sad because of you.
But I have no one to complain about you other than you.
I am here. I am here.
Listen, Nur. Right here and now.
Say yes to the biggest command I will ever have for you.
Nur.
Marry me.
This is dumb.
This is insanity.
This doesn't make any sense.
Yes. Yes, it doesn't make any sense.
You are the one thing that made no sense to me.
You still have a chance to get away. If you don't accept now, you still can get away.
But if you say yes...-
Yes.
Yes. Now I can't get away from you Yigit Kozan.
I love you, Nur.
I love you with all my heart, with all my existence as much as a man could ever possibly love a woman.
I love you.
Whenever I look at you, I forget myself so much
that I end up saying 'Yes' a million times.
And every 'Yes' makes me find myself more in you, that's how much I love you, Yigit Kozan.
Is he asleep?
Yes, he is.
At first he was demanding his lamb, but after hearing a bedtime story, he forgot.
I see you never let go of that phone, do you?
Brother...
Cahit, it's okay. She is a young woman.
Where is Yigit?
I don't like the way he is the past couple days.
He seems so tense.
Everything is fine at the company, right?
There is nothing bad I know of.
Did you also had to sign those documents?
What documents?
I also don't really know.
He made me sign them the other day.
He said some minor formalities regarding smaller stocks.
I really have no idea.
Yigit. Yigit, wait.
How could we not think of anything?
How can I go inside like this?
What are we going to say to my aunt, to your aunt?
She is the mother of your deceased wife, too.
Everyone will be shocked.
And Mert?
What if he starts hating me? What if he doesn't like me?
What did we do?
-How could we just- -Ok, ok. Calm down.
Look at me.
Look me in the eyes.
From now on, it's going to be us. Us.
You, me and Mert.
There is no one I have to explain myself to in this house other than Mert.
Trust me.
Brother!
What's going on, Yaren?
Brother, it's brother Yigit.
What's with your brother?
My brother...
Yaren, speak for once! Don't worry us. What's going on?
Aunt...
My brother has married.
What?
What are you saying, Yaren?
Brother, what have you done?
After my wife has kissed the hand of my aunt,
after that I will talk to you all.
Wife?
What wife?
Did he say 'my wife'?
Wif- Shame on you.
Shame on you.
I will talk to all of you.
Be quiet.
You don't have an aunt.
I will never forgive you.
Even if I die here now because of my pain,
I will not forgive you!
Shame on you.
What is this?
Come, Nur. Let me bring you to the bedroom.
-Aunt. -Shame on you. Shame on you. How can this be?
Shame on you.
Come.
Come, my love. Sit down.
Sit down.
It is my fault.
It's all my fault.
First I will go downstairs and talk to them.
Then we'll talk.
There are important things I have to tell you.
Trust me.
Yigit.
I trust you.
Brother, have you gone mad?
I don't understand anything. Aren't you already married?
I can't deal with you, too.
I didn't want it to go down like this.
But what can I do? It's happened.
I didn't see any other way.
-Listen carefully now. I- -You!
You....
You tricked me.
You made me sign a letter of attorney.
You tricked me and divorced your wife.
You divorced my daughter by using my signature!
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
I wasn't just your aunt, I was like your mother!
I was like your father!
What did you do?
You divorced my daughter.
In addition you married your servant's niece
who was a beggar just yesterday.
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
What else can I say to you?
Shame on you.
Could I have any more words left for you?
What else is left there to say other than 'shame on you' now?
Are you insane, Brother? Are you insane? What are you doing?!
I bet he didn't even make her sign a prenup.
Yigit, for the love of God, what have you done?
Enough!
I've fallen in love!
I have fallen in love!
I loved her, I married her!
Nur is my wife.
My wife!
You can be shocked!
You can be angry! You can hit me!
Do what you want!
But you will accept that!
Nur is my wife.
Mr Yigit?
Hello Mr Yigit, can you hear me?
Good news! Your wife has woken up.
Mr Yigit, do you hear me?
I am saying your wife is awake!
Mr Yigit, congratulations.
Hello, Mr Yigit?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Mr Yigit?