The tongue only describes the little pain,
but deep pain remains speechless.
Since I have send you after my mom, I am left speechless, dad.
You wanted this.
I am going, so you can be at peace in heaven.
I packed all my things, to go to Istanbul. To stay quiet.
Aunt? Aunt, I arrived.
Woah!
Oh, Mister Tayyar, you didn't even go to the terminal.
How is she supposed to find our home from all the way back there? She doesn't know the roads, nothing.
We just left her all alone.
Isn't it enough that we opened our doors for her, so she isn't alone?
Don't expect me to throw a welcome party for someone I had to invite in.
She should have come with us after the funeral.
Tayyar, she has waited for her father's seventh day (turkish tradition, mourning of the dead). What was she supposed to do?
Listen, she only has us.
It won't work this loveless.
Listen, don't spoil that daddy's girl.
Don't place someone else's daughter over our heads on the first day.
Oh my, Tayyar, calling her someone else's daugher and stuff...
She is my niece.
Don't start with that niece -crap!
Shame on you...
Are you talking back to me?
I will kill you.
-I am gonna kill you. -Mister Tayyar.
I accidently hit the bowl with my hand, Mrs Aytul...
I am gonna clean it up immediately.
Make Mr Yigit's Car ready, Mister Tayyar.
Will do it now, Mrs Aytul!
Listen to me.
You won't spoil that ---!
She will be thank full that we opened our doors and sit here and be quiet, get it?
Kozan- To Kozan's Farm, is it still far?
We passed it 2 km before, Miss.
Why don't you tell me? Stop, I also want to get off here.
Her father died, she is left alone. Why is he so full of hate, I don't understand.
He calls her 'someone else's daughter'.
She is trusted to me by my brother.
If I don't look after her, who else will?
Honey, I am cleaning up the table, you already had breakfast, right?
I did, I did.
Elmas, don't be like your father.
Don't make your uncle's daughter feel like a stranger, ok?
Yes, mom, spare me with this in the morning.
Look, today I have a very important meeting with Mister Yigit, don't hold me up.
I have to organize some files anyway.
Mister Yigit is driving really fast.
I am afraid something might happen.
That's his hobby.
What is this?
Bro, are we dreaming?
An angel without wings in the middle of the forest.
Hey!
Are you lost?
Did you swallow your tongue?
Let us drop you off.
Or did you not like us?
Get lost!
Bro, this one is really angry.
I said get lost already!
What if we don't?
Keep driving!
Come back, girl, don't be scared.
My beautiful, where are you going?
-Help! -Run! Run! Run!
Someone help me!
Help!
Don't come any closer!
Oh, now we are really scared.
Come on! Stop being so troublesome! Or worse could happen to you.
-I said don't come closer! -What's going on here?
None of your business.
That's brother Yigit.
They are running away! Do something!
Call the police! I am gonna report them!
Oh, I get it! Being a hero ends here for you!
They should just run away!
Where did I end up here?! What kind of people are you?!
Is this how you thank someone?
You want me to thank you for the ploy you just pulled with your friends?!
My friends?
You are kinda paranoid, aren't you?
Paranoid? Is that so?
I've been attacked by some bandits just two minutes ago.
Now the leader of the bandits let them escape.
But I am paranoid, right?
Leader of the bandits?
Are these bandits supposed to be my friends?
I thought I was helping you.
Well, you people from Istanbul are known to be helpful, truly.
You, whereever you are from, have a really friendly way of speaking.
-Are you okay? -Don't come closer!
Do whatever you want then.
It's obvious that you are lost. Where do you want to go?
None of your business.
I am trying to help you.
I don't want help.
Don't be stubborn.
Listen, you are in the forest-
Don't come closer!
-God, give me patience.
I said don't come closer!
Listen, no car, no cab will pass this road.
You won't find anything here.
There are some restaurants a few kilometres ahead.
If you are lucky you might find a few grillhouses in the morning.
Can't you ever be quiet?
Can't you ever listen?
Look, I am asking for the last time. Where are you going?
To the god damn Kozan's Farm, ok?!
You are going in the wrong direction.
Did someone ask you for the way?
Stop arguing.
Jump in, let me drive you.
What's your problem?
What do you want from me?
I don't want any help.
You won't find the house like this. Jump in.
Are you crazy? Are you dumb?
Did someone want your help?
Come here.
What are you doing? You maniac! What are you doing?!
Help me!
Stop the car!
Someone help me!
We are going to the god damn Kozan's Farm.
You psychopath!
I want to get off! Let me go!
Are you sick? Why don't you let me go?
Enjoy your meal.
Anything else, Mrs Aytul?
No, thank you.
I did already prepare the ground beef for the young man. Should I make cook dumplings or meat balls for lunch?
He keeps saying meat balls all morning.
You make him meat balls, he can eat dumplings with us to dinner.
Ok.
Where are we here?!
What's going on Hafize?
It's Mister Yigit's Car.
And someone is with him.
Where are we? Are you crazy? Say something!
My god, Nur!
Hafize, what's going on?
Slow down!
Are you crazy, or what?!
Woah! What are you doing?! I am gonna report you!
You kidnapped me to the top of the mountain!
Aunt?
Elmas?
Welcome to the god damn Kozan Farm.
-My child, how did you come here? -Welcome.
-Yigit, what's going on? -Nothing, Aunt.
Elmas, your cousin came. You are free for today.
But we had a meeting today, Mister Yigit. I can see Nur in the evening.
Nur.
Ok, you are free.
-Mister Tayyar. -Yes.
The suitcase of the miss is left on the road.
-Can you get someone to pick it up? -Yes, Mister Yigit. Immediately.
I was freaking out all morning how you would find your way here.
But not in 40 years would I have guessed that you would come in Mister Yigit's Car.
Aunt.
Is this man, the Yigit Kozan you would always talk about?
He is like a thug.
ssshh, keep quiet girl!
How can you call him a thug?
Mister Yigit is our boss.
You said every bad thing you could have said to that man.
I didn't say enough.
I don't know how we are gonna look at Mrs Aytul's face ever again after that.
Well, nevermind. Make yourself ready. Let's go thank them.
I didn't even hug you yet.
What did my brother say back then? 'God damn Kozan Farm'?
She got a big mouth.
But she is beautiful, kinda posh.
After all that timing they are working for us, you did want to do right by taking her in, but...
I hope we won't regret it, Mrs Aytul.
This is the Kozan Farm.
Everyone knows their place here.
And those who don't, will learn.
My child, let's not upset Mrs Aytul.
She is the old Madam here. She is also like Yigit's mother, she is also his aunt, she is also his-
And his?
There is no and, you be polite, that's enough. Come on!
Mrs Aytul. That's my niece Nur.
I am sorry. We regret that she came here with all that noise.
She would like to kiss your hand and apologize. Come on, my child.
No need. Welcome.
Thank you.
Hafize, dress the child appropriately.
She should not run around with open blouse and chest.
I am sorry, Mrs Aytul.
My button must have fallen off, when I was trying to escape from your nephew.
My child, how can you talk back to Mrs Aytul? Are you trying to get me in trouble?
Let's go in the kitchen.
You are in good mood.
Yes, I am.
But I am late. Gotta go now.
It's clear that you will be very busy.
Should we wait for you for dinner tonight?
No, no need. I will be coming back late.
Will you be at the company all day?
Yes.
Maybe if you find the time, I was thinking we could go for a visit.
Where is Mert?
In his room.
He is being punished.
A kid who is in first grade should not make that much trouble.
He had a report for the first half of the year anyway.
He didn't go to school. Now he is really spoiled, that brat.
Every day a new misbehavior.
Don't indulge on him.
Once you do, he doesn't listen at all.
Ok. I will talk to him.
Ok.
Grandma, grandma! I have a surprise for you. Can you come to my room?!
Mert?
Mert!
Look at him. Look at him.
What's going on? What's this noise?
Oh no, dad. You were here also?
Yeah, I am also here. What's going on?
What else could it be? Our mister here did lay a trap again.
I see. My child, are you not sick of getting punished by your Grandma?
I swear, I am sick of it, but you aren't.
-I am sick of it, but... -But?
You are sick, but you keep doing it Come here.
My child, be well behaved.
I am getting angry.
I am not doing it for you guys to get angry.
I am doing it, so my mom gets angry.
If she sees me misbehave, maybe she will come to scold me.
Why did you say that now?
Look at me.
No more messing around. You will be well behaved.
And don't say stuff like that.
Man's word?
-A man's word. -Ok.
Wait!
You didn't take your picture.
You are the tall one.
The angel is my mom.
She has huge wings.
She swung both of them and came back to us.
You gave a man's word. Don't forget that.
There is a pond, do you see it?
And...
back there are the barns.
We are just missing sheeps and cows, you understand.
It's beautiful.
It's like back at our place. My dad would love it, if he could see it.
Yeah. It's really like back there.
Istanbul, but outside of the inner city life.
Well, weekend comes and we can take you to real Istanbul.
If you lock yourself in this Farm like my parents,
you can't say 'I am living in Istanbul'.
You are bored.
Well, if Mister Yigit wasn't here, I would die of boredom.
I am working with him, as you know.
At Kozan's.
In a big plaza.
In the Levent district. In the middle of civilization!
I will drive.
What a rude man.
He must be in a bad mood.
I feel sorry for you. It must be hard working for him.
I can't say Mister Yigit is the easiest man to be around.
But he is my biggest chance.
My only chance is to work with Mister Yigit.
He is very different.
He seems like a smug rich person.
Don't think of him as one of the rich born lucky people.
He build his own luck.
One by one.
Slowly, all by his own, did he climb the latter to wealth.
He didn't count on anyone.
He came to Istanbul without his parents.
Who knows? Maybe the wealth he owns now is nothing compared to the hard work he put in.
Mister Yigit is a big man.
A very big man.
When someone gets as big as him, one gets tougher.
His inside is different. His outside is different.
Tough. Stiff.
And even as you said sometimes rude.
But his inside is very different. He is very different next to his son.
He has a son?
May god give his wife strength.
Is his wife the woman with the curly hair?
No way. That witch is- You know his brother Mister Cahit.
She is his wife.
My child, stop with the gossip.
Darling, Nur. You must be tired from the trip. Take a bath and relax.
Since you are free today, dress yourself and come help me.
Aunt, I can help you.
No, my child, you are tired from traveling.
Well then.
Listen, what did you talk about?
Mister Yigit here, Mister Yigit there.
Girl, don't tell me you did say anything to her?
My god, mother, calm down for once.
I didn't say anything.
Ah, my girl, don't get us in trouble.
If Mister Yigit finds out, we will be thrown out.
You don't say?
Because I couldn't learn what to say and what not after all this time.
Also I know better than all of you what Mister Yigit is sensitive about.
Unbelievable.
Ah, my child, you are tired from traveling. Elmas could have done that.
How can she be tired from morning till evening, Hafize?
Of course she is gonna do something. Is she supposed to lay around all day?
And let her help you in the kitchen tomorrow.
And talk to Mrs Aytul, she shall put you next to her as help.
I can help my aunt any time, uncle.
But you don't have to ask anyone for a job.
I will start searching for a job tomorrow.
You are gonna search for a job?
My child, this is Istanbul. Not Adana.
Over here the bread is not in the lion's mouth, but in his stomach. (turkish saying: it's hard to make a living)
Especially for someone like you, who hasn't seen a college in her life.
Ah, if you think to make money in a different way, then I don't know.
In case you didn't come here to earn money the righteous way.
If you say 'I want to earn my money with my youth and my beauty', then I don't know.
My, my, what kind of things are you saying, Mister Tayyar?
I wanted it to be said once.
I don't want trouble just because she is beautiful, tall, what not.
Listen, my child.
If you came here trusting on your beauty, you and I will have a lot of problems.
I don't trust my beauty. I trust my mind, uncle.
You don't worry.
By the way Nur, what's with your education?
First I will find a job that earns me enough for myself.
Then I will go take the SAT and hopefully get into university.
Hopefully.
You would want to move out in the future.
Right?
That will hopefully happen, too, uncle. I wouldn't want to burden you any longer.
What happened with your high income officer father?
He turned to sand
and his daughter is now dependent on Tayyar, who he never liked.
Enjoy the meal. I will get some fresh air.
Don't play with your food.
Finish your plate.
I don't want to.
My dad still isn't home.
He will be hungry again tonight.
He won't be hungry. He is eating outside.
Your dad is working for you.
I do have everything. Why does he keep working?
Why do you have it all, big guy?
Because your dad is working, right?
Can my dad get everything when he works?
Of course!
When he can get everything, why doesn't he get my mom back from heaven?
Come on, little lamb. Since you don't want to eat, go brush your teeth and go to bed, ok?
Come here, little lamb.
When he keeps going like this, it seems like, we won't be able to send him back to school.
Yigit must get another report then.
What nonsense are you talking, Nazan?
You may not want to know it, Mrs Aytul, but your grandson is still waiting for his mom from heaven.
When he keeps talking weird stuff like that, do you think Yigit would dare to send him to elementary school?
God protect us, what if he draws someone's attention?
Or I don't know if someone comes to him and tells him the truth?
Nazan, don't stick your nose into things that are not your business.
I assume, Yigit doesn't plan to stay all night, right?
Did you talk to him when leaving the office?
I did knock at his door, but he didn't answer.
You didn't get an answer, but opening the door and taking a look, didn't cross your mind, right, Cahit?
Your little brother didn't want you to disturb his peace, didn't he?
I didn't want to disturb him, Nazan.
It's getting cold here at night.
You will get a cold.
By the way I am Yigit.
I know your name.(She uses polite form)
Oh, you went from calling me a maniac to talking politely.
I also know your name, but we didn't really get to meet eachother.
I thought we met in the car.
I am Nur.
You should go inside.
It's cold.
Don't get a cold.
Good night.
And you are supposed to be a big brother? A big brother that can't even go into the room of his little brother, if he doesn't invite him in.
You are the older one, Cahit. And can't even stand tall against your little brother.
Where is Mert? Is he here?
I just put him to bed.
Aunt, is Mert with you? Is he downstairs?
Girl, you said you put him to bed, where is this kid?
What's going on, Yigit?
Mert isn't in his room, did you see him?
What's going on?
Did he... ?
Cahit, run. Run!
Mom! Mom!
I am here, mom.
Mommy, I am here. I am here.
Come to me.
Come on.
I am here.
I am here, mommy.
Come to me.
Come on.
Mert! Mert!
Mert! Where are you?!
Come on, Yigit, calm down.
Calm down, for what?!
Tayyar! Tayyar!
-I beg you, calm down. -Calm for what?!
You are so many people and can't even keep an eye on one kid!
He didn't do it for so long. I told you so many times, let's lock his door, but you wouldn't listen.
Mert!
Mert?
How did you get up there?
Don't be scared. I am coming.
Keep calm.
Mom!
Wait. Don't move.
I want my mom!
Come here. Come to me.
Mert? Mert!
Brother! Brother, come here!
Where is he?
Mert! What are you doing there?!
Don't let my dad come here.
He will bring me down.
Stop! Stop, his dad!
We are going down now.
I am coming! Don't move!
I am not even scared!
My mom is gonna come now!
I am not scared!
Don't move! I am on my way!
Come on, Mert. Give me your hand.
Let's go back.
I won't! I am gonna hold my mom's hand!
Let's go.
Mert!
Ok.
Let's go. Come on.
-Hug me tight now. -Mert!
Come here!
Wait, his dad. Wait, we are coming down.
Give him to me.
Come here.
Come here, come.
What do you think you are doing?!
What do you think you are doing?!!
You won't do anything like this ever again! Do you understand!?
You won't!
I will! I will! I am gonna do it, till my mom comes back!
Your mom won't come back, do you understand?!
Your mom won't come!
You liar! My mom is gonna come back!
You said it yourself!
From the clouds, from the stars, from heaven, she will come back!
-Your mom won't come back! -That's enough!
Don't scream at the child!
Give me my grandson.
Come here my boy.
He will not come out of his room!
Did you hear me?! He will not come out of his room!
Yigit, calm dow-
Brother, please! Please.
Why is this here?! Huh?!
Who brought this here?!
We wanted to cut the branches. We must have forgotten-
Don't start with your branches!
-Bring me the saw! Now! -Yes, Sir!
Nur. Nur.
I am coming, aunt. I just want to catch my breath.
He missed his mom a lot.
Try to be a little understanding.
Tayyar!
Where is the saw?!
I am coming, Sir.
Here you go.
What are you doing? Have you gone crazy?
Out of my way.
You punished your son already
now you want to punish the tree, too?
I said, out of my way. It's none of your business.
If you do something like that, is your fear gonna vanish?
You locked him into his room.
What happened? Is your fear gone?
You are scared! A lot!
As long as you keep punishing your son,
instead of understanding him, you will always be scared.
I don't like my dad.
I don't.
Why does he say that my mom won't come?
Heaven was going to give my mom back.
Why is my mom not coming? Why?
I feel like I am going to dream of that child tonight.
How he was reaching out to the stars calling for his mother.
It's clear in front of my eyes.
What happened to his mom?
A car accident.
Three years ago.
He really misses his mom.
Like he has not accepted her death.
He thinks she is going to come back.
It's sad.
Very sad.
Why don't you understand, Iclal? Why?
It doesn't work and it won't work.
You know exactly how it all started.
It was wrong from the very beginning.
You know that my aunt did plan all this.
It was all wrong from the very beginning, Iclal.
I love you, Yigit.
Iclal.
You do love me? Then why is life a living hell for us?
Why are we waking up and fighting? Why are we arguing every day?
Look, Iclal.
I want to divorce you.
Do you understand? I want to divorce you.
You want to divorce me, huh?
Yes.
-You want to have a life without me? -Yes!
But for me there is no life without you, Yigit.
If you are not here, then there is no life here!
Iclal, what are you doing?!
-Let go! -Stop!
Ms Iclal might open her eyes now or after many years.
Or even never wake up.
Three years! You say that for 3 years!
When will the mother of my child wake up?!
When?!
Time is ticking.
Your wife might never wake up.
We all get wounded with time. Small, big.
Small, big.
Deep.
We all have many small wounds here and there.
Time...
helps close some wounds.
Some you can't even see, or even feel.
But some, even when they are only scars, never stop bleeding.
Time... doesn't heal every wound.
They may be hidden from the eyes. But the heart feels them.
Yigit Kozan.
A proud, rude, cruel man.
But seems like you are also deeply wounded, like I am.
Dad! Dad! A balloon tree!
For you, my son!
A balloon tree!
Mert! Your feet are naked, Mert.
Dad!
Are you running around with bare feet?
You are gonna catch a cold.
Be careful not to step on something sharp. Come.
Good boy!
Did you do that for me, dad?
Of course, for you!
Come up.
Won't you be mad?
Why should I be mad, my son? Come on.
You were angry last night.
But now I am here.
Come, come, come.
Woop, Superman!