Brother, what have you done?
After my wife has kissed the hand of my aunt,
after that I will talk to you all.
Wife?
What wife?
Did he say 'my wife'?
Wif- Shame on you.
Shame on you.
Aunt.
I will talk to all of you.
Be quiet.
You don't have an aunt.
I will never forgive you.
Even if I die here now because of my pain,
I will not forgive you!
Shame on you.
What is this?
Come, Nur. Let me bring you to the bedroom.
-Aunt. -Shame on you. Shame on you. How can this be?
Shame on you.
Come.
Come, my love. Sit down.
Sit.
It is my fault.
It's all my fault.
First I will go downstairs and talk to them.
Then we'll talk.
There are important things I have to tell you.
Trust me.
Yigit.
I trust you.
Brother, have you gone mad?
I don't understand anything. Aren't you already married?
I can't deal with you, too.
I didn't want it to go down like this.
But what can I do? It's happened.
I didn't see any other way.
-Listen carefully now. I- -You!
You...
You tricked me.
You made me sign a letter of attorney.
You tricked me and divorced your wife.
You divorced my daughter by using my signature!
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
I wasn't just your aunt, I was like your mother!
I was like your father!
And what did you do?
You divorced my daughter.
In addition you married your servant's niece
who was a beggar just yesterday.
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
What else can I say to you?
Shame on you.
Could I have any more words left for you?
What else is left there to say other than 'shame on you' now?
Are you insane, Brother? Are you insane? What are you doing?!
I bet he didn't even make her sign a prenup.
Yigit, for the love of God, what have you done?
Enough!
I've fallen in love!
I have fallen in love!
I loved her, I married her!
Nur is my wife.
My wife!
You can be shocked!
You can be angry! You can beat me up!
Do what you want!
But you will accept that!
Nur is my wife.
Mr Yigit?
Hello Mr Yigit, can you hear me?
Good news! Your wife has woken up.
Mr Yigit, do you hear me?
I am saying your wife has woken up!
Mr Yigit, congratulations.
Hello, Mr Yigit?
Hello? Hello, can you hear me?
Mr Yigit?
Aunt.
You are like my mother to me.
I never forgot the work you have put into me, nor my son- not even a day.
I tricked you.
I did.
I divorced your daughter by tricking you.
You wouldn't have understood. You wouldn't have listened.
I wronged you, Aunt.
I wronged you.
But this wrong I did to you and your daughter
I did on the day I married your daughter without loving her.
You put my girl in the ground before she died.
Nur?
Schlange.
You sneaky snake.
-You are a snake. -Aunt.
A phone call for you.
-Now is not the time. Please call again later. -Mr Yigit! Congratulations!
Your wife woke up.
Mr Yigit? Can you hear me?
I am saying your wife has woken up.
Hello, Mr Yigit?
Hello?
Hello, can you hear me?
Mr Yigit?
What is happening, Yigit?
Brother, what is happening? Speak already.
Yigit, speak! What is going on?
Iclal...
Iclal?
Did she die, Yigit?
Iclal woke up.
She is out of the coma.
She woke up...
She woke up.
Aunt! Aunt.
Aunt.
She came out of the coma.
You...
You lied to me.
You said your wife died.
You said she's dead.
Nur. Don't leave.
Don't touch.
Don't touch me.
My daughter...
-Bring me to my daughter.  -Ok.
-Cahit, bring me to my daughter. -Ok, Aunt.
I will get the car immediately.
My daughter...
What are you still doing here?
Have you not heard, your wife has woken up?
Your wife has woken up.
The one, who you divorced with trickery and lies just yesterday,
the mother of your child, has woken up.
What are you doing?
What are you going to do?
Are you not coming with us?
Say what you are going to do?!
-Are you going to have your wedding night with her?! What are you going to do?! -Aunt!
Come on, let's go. The car is ready.
Nazan, you stay here and have an eye on Mert, ok?
Sure. Sure.
You lied to me.
I wanted to tell you everything, Nur.
I swear to you, I wanted to tell you everything.
You lied to me.
No.
I didn't lie to you.
I hid the truth, yes.
But I didn't lie, Nur.
I didn't lie.
Yigit.
I can't stall our Aunt any longer. Let's go please.
Wait here for me.
I beg you, please wait here for me.
Dad, why are you being so loud?
You woke me up.
Where are you going?
Come, Mert. Your dad has stuff to do. I will put you back to bed.
Nur can bring me to bed.
Nur, come one. Bring me to bed.
My, what a sly one she is.
Still in her wedding dress, but she took the kid by his hand and did go anyways.
You listen to me!
You will leave them alone.
You won't say one word to Mert.
Got it?
Before we know for sure that his mother is alright,
you won't say anything to my son.
Got it?!
You look just like the fairy out of the stories my aunt told me.
Where you also scared of Aunt Nazan?
Come now. Fall asleep.
Don't be scared. I will protect you.
Can you tell me a bed time story?
Thank god, I am reunited with my son again.
Sweet home.
I really missed it!
And your mother missed you, my dear.
Come on, Hafize, come on.
Because his bus was stuck in traffic, I am starving.
Hurry up, Hafize.
I am saying I am starving and you still blabber.
Nur probably has made dinner alrea-
Yeah... She did.
God knows, on what fun trip the young Lady is today.
There is no way.
She probably just took a nap. Go, Elmas, wake her up.
Ok.
And you, my dear, can take a nice bath.
Dinner should be ready by the time you are out.
Alright? My big lion.
Nur isn't here.
What?
Mrs Iclal?
Can you hear me?
Your finger. You only have to move one finger.
Out of my way. I want to see my daughter.
Miss, you can't go in like that, please.
What do you mean by I can't? I am going to see my daughter!
The doctor is going to meet you in his office first. Please don't cause any trouble.
-Doctor, I want to see my daughter. -Please calm down. You will see Miss Iclal soon.
But first we need to talk.
My friend is doing the last tests.
Please follow me.
Mr Yigit?
Hello Mr Yigit? Can you hear me?
Good news.
Your wife woke up.
I wanted to tell you everything, Nur. I swear I wanted to tell you everything.
I did hide the truth, yes.
But I didn't lie, Nur.
Wait here for me.
Please I beg you, wait for me.
My beautiful daughter.
Welcome back, my daughter.
Good morning, my dear.
Good morning, my daughter.
My sweet girl.
Doesn't she see me? Why doesn't she look me in my face?
It's too early to expect our patient to react normal to her environment.
We know she is aware of us for now.
That is enough for us.
Please don't tire her too much.
I am going to the laboratory and will be right back.
My lovely child.
My beautiful daughter.
Tell me.
Tell me, my dear.
What do you want from your mother, tell me, my dear.
Yigit.
Your wife...
is asking for you.
Yigit.
Iclal.
Welcome back.
Let's not tire our patient any longer please.
We have to start with the tests. You can wait outside.
Are you still here, knock-off bride?
Some only dream of things, that others are destined to.[proverb]
The wedding night turned to the night of painful tears.
You know I had a bad feeling about you, the first time I saw you.
I saw your hungry eyes lust after everything here, but
even I couldn't imagine this much, to be honest.
I don't know if you are a witch or a healer, but you can sweet talk yourself into anything.
But your luck has run dry.
I mean, the sleeping beauty who was asleep like a baby,
wakes up out of nowhere on your wedding night.
Well, even a good player gets a bad hand sometimes.
I didn't know that Mert's mother is alive.
Your aunt and uncle really have a tight mouth. Impressive.
Good job, from them. They really are worth every penny.
Well, since you know everything now, why are you still here?
Are you waiting to spend your wedding night with a husband who went to his hidden wife?
I came here believing in Yigit's words
and looking into his eyes.
Don't worry.
He will say what he has to say
and I will leave while looking into the same eyes again.
How is my daughter, Doctor?
We have to be very very careful in this early stage.
The transition from coma to a normal life is a risky period and demands small cautious steps.
The tests we are running will take a few days.
-We will inform you in the following days. -Inform us?
I will be here anyways, I am not going anywhere.
Mrs Aytul, I told you already it won't help you nor your daughter to be staying here.
We have to let her rest.
The following days are crucial.
You have to rest and be strong, too.
When will we have the results of the tests?
We will tell you before noon.
-I wish you a nice morning. -Thank you.
Brother, what's going on?
I will tell you on the ride home. We are leaving.
You heard the doctor, Aunt.
It doesn't do any good to stay here. Come on.
Let's rest for a few hours and come back with Mert in the afternoon.
-We won't tell Mert anything, Aunt. -Why not?
My daughter will be reunited with her child.
You heard the doctor, Aunt.
I can't play with my son's feelings before knowing for sure how Iclal's situation is.
If I'm going to tell him 'Your mom is healthy again. She is coming back.'
I must be sure it's true.
I can't tell him that while being afraid.
You are not afraid of my daughter's death,
you are afraid that she might live.
I will pretend I didn't hear that, Aunt.
Because I have to look you in the eyes.
If you have a heart, turn around and look me in the eyes.
Look at me!
You were driving the car that fateful night.
3 years...
Exactly for 3 years
day and night
I was in pain every single day.
And even then I didn't blame you. I didn't say it's your fault.
But now I am clinging to your collar and I am begging you.
As your substitute mother.
As a mother, I am begging you.
You started this fire.
Now put it out.
Nur.
Marry me.
Nur!
Where is she?
Now I am done for. I am done for.
I am done for. Where is this girl again?
Mrs Aytul! Mrs Aytul!
I beg you, please help me.
What's going on so early in the morning?
Nur! Nur is missing.
I fell asleep yesterday and now she is nowhere to be found.
I was thinking of going to the police. Maybe by car- No, maybe we should call a taxi.
If I tell Tayer, he will kill me and not let me go anywhere.
You don't need to go anywhere. Your niece isn't missing.
No...
How can that be? It can't be.
My niece wouldn't do something like that.
I don't know what can or cannot be.
But what I tell you is the truth.
Your niece did go back to Adana.
She came to me, told me she doesn't want to stay here with you any longer.
No way.
There is no way that can be.
All her things are still in her room. How can someone leave without a suitcase or anything?
Behave yourself, Hafize!
Are you questioning me?!
No, how could I?
I have dealt enough with your family problems.
If I say your niece left, she left.
And you are free for a few days.
Don't come into the house without being called.
Aunt!
Why did you do that?
Why did you lie?
She literally is my brother's wife. She is at home.
Whatever I told Hafize is true.
I will give money into that girl's pocket and she will leave.
This wedding will be over.
And no one will know of this disgrace.
I waited for you.
Not because you wanted me to. Because I wanted to.
Because I wanted to ask you one question.
Why?
Why did you do this to me?
Why?!
Why did you trick me?!
What will happen now, Aunt?
What if she doesn't want to go back to Adana?! What if our lie gets exposed?
Cahit is showering. I told him to sleep, but...
I couldn't get an ounce of sleep last night.
I get goosebumps whenever I think of it.
It's unbelievable.
Exactly 3 years and she woke up at the day of her husband's wedd-
Nazan!
You can say what you want, Mrs Aytul.
It's like Iclal figured out what happened to her and woke up immediately.
What happened?
I am dying of curiosity.
Did she say or ask something?
Is this girl upstairs?
Of course.
In fact I think Yigit also went upstairs a moment ago.
What ever they are doing...
She is very obedient.
She waited for her husband at the window all night.
Listen to yourself!
This marriage has no meaning.
Don't ever forget this.
No one should.
You have to tell this to the girl now, Mrs Aytul.
She didn't even take off her wedding dress.
I don't think this girl is one to easily get rid off.
You heard it from me first.
I ask for your son's mother's grave.
I tried to share your pain like an idiot.
I tried to understand you.
And you! What did you do?!
You tricked me!
While you said you love me,
While you held my hand,
while I said that I am in love with you,
you were married! Married!
While I loved you, she was asleep.
Say something, you monster!
When did you want to tell me?! When?!
I was scared.
I was afraid I might lose you.
You lost me.
The day we united was the day you lost me.
The day we have waited for years has arrived.
A miracle has happened.
But I... can't even look my daughter in the eyes.
I couldn't even tell my son the good news.
Oh, right, we forgot about Sinan.
What's the time in america right now?
Mr Yigit must put out this fire.
I will call Sinan after the situation has cooled down.
Aunt.
You should rest up and sleep a bit.
I cannot sleep as long as this ****** is upstairs.
Aunt.
She is a *****, isn't she?
Aunt!
What do you think you are doing?
I am leaving. Don't worry.
We will get divorced immediately.
You won't see me ever again.
Do you think I am stupid?
On you this miserable wedding dress,
you will run to the out-building and cry.
After crying out to your aunt, you will put us in the hands of that sly uncle of yours.
I don't even understand what you are trying to say.
Who do you think you are fooling?
No one is going to see you like this.
Just as you quietly sneaked your way into my nephew's heart,
you will leave this house just as quietly.
If you tell your aunt and uncle just one word,
if you tell anyone about this fake marriage,
I won't let you pay the price, but them.
I won't show any mercy and throw them out of here.
Do you understand?
You are threatening me in vein.
Even if you don't believe me,
I have been just as tricked as you were.
This is enough humiliation.
-I don't want to share this [humiliation] with my aunt. -Be quiet.
Nazan.
Help this shameless girl change into something else and give her some money.
Without anyone seeing, send her off through the service door.
You will go to Adana.
Your family believe you to be there anyways.
'Believe me to be there anyways'?
They asked about you in the morning.
And my aunt...
What are you doing?!
Let me go!
Let me go! Don't touch me!
What are you doing?! Let me go!
I said let go!
I am telling you to let go!
Let go!
-Get inside! -Let go! -Get inside!
Sit down! You will listen to me!
Exactly 3 years! For 3 years she was asleep!
For 3 years...
I didn't know what to say to my son.
'You don't have a mother anymore.'
I couldn't say: 'Actually you do and you don't.'
I also couldn't say: 'Wait. She might wake up one day.'
'Don't wait. We need a miracle for her to wake up.'
'Your mother has died.', I couldn't say.
I made up a fairy tale that she will come from heaven.
That fairy tale made him fall asleep at night.
I hid everything.
Everything. I used my power, my money, my all.
I turned Iclal to a secret no one dares to talk about.
I deleted all news, all details about the accident.
I fired everyone who only dared to look like they might question me.
I calculated everything.
I thought of everything.
Just one thing I missed.
You.
Love.
Don't dare talk about love.
Love has died for me, yesterday at this farm.
It has died on the grounds it had been born.
You fooled your son.
You fooled your aunt, who took you in like a mother.
You fooled me.
You have fooled everyone who loved you.
What lie do you know of?
You just don't know of all the truths.
I don't want your truth.
I don't even want to see your face.
Go out of my way.
You won't go anywhere!
What are you doing?! What are you doing?!
Are you going to lock me up in this room?!
Yes.
Are you insane?!
Yigit! Are you insane?! Open the door!
I am insane!
With all my heart!
He has lost it.
He locked her up in the room for real.
Why can't I just die?
Aunt.
Please don't move, I can't measure like this.
I think he is coming.
You promised me.
I said 'Put out the fire' and you promised me. What are doing, huh?
What are you doing?! What are you doing?!
I know!
I promised!
I will fix everything for everyone, Aunt.
I will find a wway.
Nur...
my wife
While my wife is here
While my wife is with me, I will find a way, Aunt.
Yaren.
Go out with Mert when he is awake.
Go to the cinema, do whatever you want.
Just keep him away from the house.
You take Elmas and go to the company.
Cancel every meeting.
-Yigit, can we-  -Later.
Later.
Nazan, go bring me Hafize.
She is probably worried by now, I have to tell her everything.
Here?
Here!
Hurry up!
Sister-in-law!
We can't do that, Brother.
We told [politely called]Aunt Hafize that Nur has gona back to Adana.
You did what?!
Another lie?!
Yigit.
This way...
things will stay calmer.
Mom, please stop crying.
Nur will call us for sure.
Maybe she felt overwhelmed or maybe she went to water the graves of her parents.
And would she leave without seeing me?
She left, son.
Without even saying good bye to her aunt, she just left.
Hadn't Mrs Aytul herself told me, I would have never believed it.
So she is someone who can just leave like that.
My... Mom, Emin is right.
She probably just needed a break.
If she told you, you would have made a big deal out of it.
Seems like she wanted some time to think
and went to Adana.
She will call, don't worry.
If she doesn't, we can call her.
What was the name of their neighbors? The ones with the daughter.
We can ask them.
Don't you worry.
Only bad things come to my mind.
What if that maniac found her?
What maniac?
Don't you remember that one troublemaker, that psycho? She's talking about him.
No, I can't just sit here.
Hafize.
If your hand reaches that phone for that shameless girl,
I will bring your hands, one by one. Just so you know.
What?
Don't you like the way I talk to your mom?
Mother's son.
I will be heading off to work now. See you later.
Have a nice day at work, my child.
Good morning, Mr Cahit.
Good morning.
We'll be going with my car today.
And Mr Yigit?
Yigit won't come to work today.
But he has many meetings today.
Is he sick?
He doesn't feel well.
You have to cancel the meetings.
Let's go.
Cahit, tell me already, what happened?
Elmas, it's personal. Regarding the family.
Please don't pressure me.
Since you came, and he didn't, it's something regarding Mr Yigit.
The only person you care about is Mr Yigit, isn't it?
What does that have to do with anything?
I am his assistant basically.
What do you mean?
How often are you going to be jealous of Mr Yigit, Cahit? We have talked about this many times.
-He isn't someone like this for me. I just-      -...admire him.
That he is so successful.
His power.
You admire the way he carries himself.